我会记得人们常说我们转向第一人称
I will remember people often often said that we move to first person
因为这更容易，因为我们看不到玩家角色
Because it's easier because we don't see player characters
只是说你是否会看到我们在《巫师》中的图表
just say if you would see the graphs that we had in witcher
以及赛博朋克中的图表
And the graphs that we have in cyberpunk
没有十倍大的
There are no ten times bigger
嗨，我是。迈克尔，欢迎来到频道故事模式
Hi i'm . michael and welcome to story mode the channel
我们探索视频游戏讲故事的力量
We explore the storytelling power of video games
今天我们正在玩《赛博朋克二十七十七》的几个早期任务
today we are playing through a couple early missions of cyber punk twenty seventy seven
并讨论以完全第一人称视角制作游戏所带来的独特的讲故事挑战
And discussing the unique storytelling challenges that come with doing a game in a entirely first person perspective
我加入了故事模式团队的一部分 alex coyotes 你好
I am joined by part of the story mode team alex coyotes hello
控制器上的压力就是它的原因
And on the controller is why it's strain
你好
hello
我们很高兴拥有资深电影设计师 pavl ohazski
And we're excited to have senior cinematic designer pavl ohazski
叙事导演伊戈·沙辛斯基
And narrative director ego shazinski
欢迎小伙伴们来到节目
Guys welcome to the show
你好你好
Hello hello
名字怎么样，还好吗
How how was the names were they okay
还不错
it wasn't too too bad
真的很好
Really good
就像，是的
Like , yeah
哈哈哈哈
Ha ha ha h
你知道，所以是五百七。太棒了
You know , so it's five hundred of seven . is it's great
好的
Okay
我会接受的
I will take that
我肯定会接受的
I will take that for sure
一
Um
好的
Okay
所以我真的很高兴能和你们谈论，呃
So i'm really excited to talk to you guys about , uh
我们要涉及的所有事情因为我
All the things we're gonna get into because i
你知道，我记得启动赛博朋克
You know , i remember booting up cyberpunk
我清理了我的日程安排
I cleared my schedule
整个故事我读得很开心
I had so much fun going through the whole story
并进入游戏
And going into the game
我当时有点
I was a little
呃，担心是因为我没玩过那么多第一人称RPG
Uh , concern because i hadn't played that many first person rpg
大部分都是像第三人称那样做的
Had mostly done like the third person thing
所以我很好奇如何
So i was very curious about how
那次经历会是什么样子
What that experience was going to look like
以及所有这些讲故事的时刻将如何完成
And how all those storytelling moments were going to be done
我对第一人称的承诺感到非常震惊
And i was just super blown away by the commitment to the first person
以及所有不同的技术
and all the different techniques
你们过去常常用电影的方式讲故事
You guys used to tell a story in a cinematic way
你知道，不使用传统的电影语言
Without using , you know , conventional cinematic language
而且，你知道，相机可以剪辑以及诸如此类的东西
And , you know , the camera can cut and all that stuff
所以
So
一会儿我们要去看《巫师三》
And a moment we're gonna go to the witcher three
看看其中的一个场景来识别
and kind of look at a scene from that to identify
其中一些常规的
What some of those conventional
呃，讲故事的语言是这样的
Uh , storytelling language things are
但我只是想听听你们的消息
But i kind of just want to hear from you guys for
对于那些可能不知道什么的人
For people that might not know what
你的工作包括什么
What does your job entail
你在赛博朋克中负责什么
What are you responsible for in cyberpunk
好的
Okay
一
Um
嗯，这是一个，你知道这是一个很好的问题
Well , that's a that's , you know that's that's a great question
呃
Uh
因为我们有这个问题需要正确解释
Because we have that problem to explain properly
我们很多时间都在做什么
What we do a lot of time
呃，在我们部门，我们经常这样问自己
Uh , often we ask ourselves that , uh , in our department
还有像最近这样的
And of like recently
我们做了完整的演示
And we made our full blown presentation
如何向奶奶解释
How to explain to a grandmother
电影设计师是做什么的，对吧
What does cinematic designer does , right
这是一个问题，呃
This is a problem , uh
我觉得大部分都是这些
I think most of these
我们正在指导游戏中的叙事内容
We are directing the narratic content in our games
所以我们对它的外观负责
So we are responsible for how it looks
感觉如何。最后
How it feels . and in the end
当玩家实际浏览我们创建的内容时它是如何播放的
How it plays when player actually goes through the content that we created
呃，从我的角度来看
Uh , from my perspective
通常只是将东西放在一起
It's often about just putting stuff together
所以基本上导演在电影中所做的除了这里的例外
so basically what the director does in the movies with this exception that here
您还实现了游戏元素并考虑了交互性
You also implemented and take the interactivity into account the gameplay elements
等等
And so on
一
Um
所以这就像你有不同的部门一起工作
So it's about like you have different departments working together
任务故事的环境视觉特效
Environment vfx out the quest story
等等 。因为电影设计师就处于其中
And so on . as the cinematic designer are kind of in the middle of it
并尝试使所有元素相互契合
And try to make all elements fit into each other
所以就像，你知道，场景很悲伤
So like , you know , the scene is sad
突然之间你就没有播放愉快的音乐了
And suddenly you don't have a happy music playing or something
仍然是，呃，这是一个简单的例子
It's still , uh , it's a simple example
但大多数时候只是将事物连接在一起
But most of the time is just about connecting things together
是的
Yeah
惊人的
Awesome
凉爽的
Cool
好的
Okay
出色地
Well
是的
Yeah
所以我们要看看《巫师三》中的场景
So we're gonna look at it scene from the witcher three
你能不能
And can you kind of
呃，当我们正在看的时候
Uh , as we're watching it
列出一些用于该类型的工具的名称
Name some of the tools that are used in that kind of
你知道，电影式的讲故事必须是，呃
You know , cinematic storytelling that had to be , uh
为赛博朋克而改变或重新思考
Changed or rethought for a cyber punk
但是你为什么要启动呢，这三个
But so why do you want to startup , which were three
是的
And yeah
你们解释一下
You guys sort of explain
这个场景中讲故事的方式是怎样的
What's going on storytelling wise in this scene
呵呵，酷
Hh , cool
其实这就是我拍的场景，我记得
Actually it's the scene i did , i remember
一
Um
是的
Yeah
所以，嗯，与猎魔人
So , um , with the witcher
我想，嗯，也是因为这是我们类似公式中的第三款游戏
I think , um , also because it's our third game in the similar formula
而且，嗯，基于当时制作的许多类似游戏的文件
And , um , based les on many similar games done at the time
嗯，游戏玩法之间的区别非常明显
Um , you have a pretty clear distinction between gameplay
就像故事的节拍一样
And like the story beats
当然，我们假设它不像零一
Let's say it's not like zero one , of course
就像它融合在不同的杠杆中一样
And like it blends in different levers
但基本上你会探索你的跑步
But basically you explore your run
你需要努力点击一些东西
You fight to click some things
然后当你想告诉你一个故事时
And then when you we want to tell you a story
然后我们进入电影级电影模式
Then we go into the cinematic ucinematic mode
而且，嗯，这样
And , um , in this way
这是一个非常经典的主题故事
It's a pretty classical thematic storytelling
所以你的相机镜头只显示你
So you have the camera shots that show you only
我们想在任何特定时刻向您展示什么
What we want to show you at any given moment
就像相机放在这里一样
So like camera goes here
镜头转到这里，镜头切回来
Camera goes here , camera cuts back
依此类推，有一个编辑
And so on there's an edit
当然
Of course
我们在场景中安排角色，嗯
We stage characters around the scene , um
但就像与编辑一起，我们可以传送它们
But like together with the edits , we can teleport them
事实上，如果你用静态外部摄像头在冬天观看这些场景中的任何一个
And actually , if you look at any of those scenes in the winter from like static external camera
您只会看到像在之间弹出的字符
You would see just characters like popping between
一直喜欢场景中的不同地方
Like different places in the scene all the time
但从玩家角度来看
But from the player perspective
它们无法在相机本身中接收
They cannot receiit in the camera itself
因为它就像，你知道，一些模糊的背景，例如，或者其他什么
Because it's just like , you know , some blurried background , for example , or something
对于我们来说，它给了我们创作的自由
And for us , it gives us like the creative freedom
比如说与背景形成完美的构图。等等
Let's say to make a perfect composition with the background . and so on
玩家通常不会看到角色移动了两米夏天
Players usually don't see that the characters moved like by two meters summer
因为有时也没有直接的参考点
Because also sometimes there are no direct points of reference
一
Um
所以，呃，演技方面就是这样
So , uh , that was it in terms of acting
我们主要是在混合，嗯
We were mostly mixing , um
呃，自定义独特的资产，比如最大的过场动画和你只看到一次的东西
Uh , custom unique assets for like the biggest cut scenes and stuff that you see only once
这正是故事的时刻
And it's exactly for the story moment
实际上有一个巨大的动画库，我们可以以多种不同的创意方式重用它们
With actually a huge library of animations that we could reuse in many different creative ways
就像拉伸动画一样
Like stretch animations
剪切它们，与其他动画混合
Cut them , blend with other animations
与更多动画等混合
Blend with more animations and so on
你会惊讶于游戏中的某些时刻
And you would be surprised like there are moments in the game where
哪些就像伸手去拿东西
Which are is like reaching for something
握住它并传递给某人
And holding it and passing into someone
但实际上我们从只用一只手演奏的喝酒动画拼凑而成
But actually we put together from the animation of drinking played only on a hand
还有上半身打开的动画什么的
And the animation of turning on the upper body and something
最后在相机里
And in the end in the camera
看起来他真的在做这件事
Kind of looks like he's really doing this
但对我们来说，这确实是一个好方法
But for us it was a really like a good way of for
就像节省录制所有自定义内容的时间一样
So like saving time on recording everything custom
就像能够在许多不同的级别上操纵动画一样
Just like being able to manipulate animations in many different levels
一
Um
呃，得到什么
Uh , get or something
是的
Yeah
我不是，也许我没有忘记
I'm not , not forget maybe
但我认为是这样
But i think it's it's
重要的是要记住我们实际上使用了普通电影所做的一切，对吧
It's very important to remember that we actually use everything that normal movies do , right
所以我们将编辑，我们使用摄像机
So we will edit , we use cam camera
我们使用，呃，角色移动，呃
We use , uh , character movement , uh
甚至从伊戈尔所说的各种简单的事情来看，非常简单的动画
And even from the various simple things like igor said , very simple animations
你可以得到玩家的这种情绪反应
You can get this emotional response for the player
因为玩家会观察动作并且能够对动作产生共鸣，对吗？
Because the player observes the action and can empathize with the action , right
这样他们就能理解角色内心深处的感受
So they can understand what the characters are feeling deep inside
我们用所有这些来讲述最好、最感人的故事
And we use all of that to tell the best , most moving stories possible
尽管我们使用的是非常基本的，呃
Even though we are using very basic , uh
你知道，就像制作工具的一百年一样，顶部还点缀着互动功能，对吧？
You know , like one hundred year in the making tools with the sprinkled interactivity on the top , right
所以在选择的时刻会玩centipeak并选择
So during the choice moments will play centipeak and choose
他们想要故事的哪个分支
Which branch of the story they want to take
嗯嗯
Uh huh
呃
Uh
是的
Yeah
这里实际上是你刚刚关闭的场景
Here actually the scenes you just shut
这正是与巴罗诺斯的场景
This was exactly does the scene with baronos
主要是在像库动画一样的起床上完成的
Mostly done on like library animations is getting up
转动一个简单的东西
Turning a simple stuff
然后一个是 sii Siri 穿过森林
And then one is sii siri running through the forest
现在她需要，嗯
And now she needs , um
呃，在树枝下什么的
Uh , under the , under the branch or something
这完全就像一个定制的时刻
It's totally like a custom moment
就，就一次，就你，呃，就这个
Just , just once , just u , uh , just this
是的
Yeah
所以是的
And so yeah
我完全喜欢你所说的
I like exactly what you said
他们的目的是，总结一下，你正在使用大约四百年来电影中的所有工具
They're pol to , to kind of summarize that you're using all the tools from film that have been around four hundred years
就像你说的自我
Like you were saying ego
您可以让摄像机准确地显示玩家
You can have the camera show the player exactly
您希望他们在任何特定时刻看到的内容
What you want them to see at any given moment
你知道，你可以剪两个特写
You know , you can cut two closeups
你可以移动镜头来强调，嗯
You can do camera moves to accentuate , um
你知道，情感和压缩的时间
You know , emotion and compressed time
你知道，就像你说的，你就像在幕后一样
And you know , like you were saying you go like behind the scenes
角色们到处跳来跳去
The characters are jumping around and all
电影场景中发生的所有事情
All the stuff that's what's happening on a movie set
是的
Yeah
正确的
Right
都是假的
It's all fake
是的
Yeah
呃
Uh
所以是的
So yeah
所以你在《巫师三》中拥有所有这些工具
So you have all those tools in the witcher three
这就是传统的电影叙事方式
And that's kind of conventional cinematic storytelling
那么为什么，为什么我们不跳进去，呃
So why , why don't we jump into , uh
网络朋克和想谈谈基本上
Cyber punk and wanna talk about basically
你们如何获得同样的情感
How you guys achieve the same kind of emotions
呃，没有那些工具或者类似的修改所有这些东西
Uh , without those tools or like by modifying all those things
但也许让我们从类似开始
But maybe let's start with just like
背后是什么样的决策
What was the kind of decision making behind
首先以第一人称视角进行赛博朋克
Doing cyber punk in first person perspective to begin with
啊，当然
Ah , sure
所以对我来说，这就像两个
So for me , these were like two
我们从以下角度来说一下这个决定的方向
Let's say directions for this decision from the point of view
让我们以某种方式说创造者和创造
Let's say creator and creation in a way
所以从创作者的角度来看，就像这样
So from the creator point of view , like this
这是公式，经典的电影公式
Which are formula , the classic cinematic formula
我我感觉我们
I i felt like we
我们在某种程度上将这个公式推向了极限
We have pushed this formula to the limit in a way
就像我们可以让它变得更好一样
Like we could make it may be better
但不会有所不同
But it won't be different
这就像一个定量的
It would be just like a quantative
不是真正的定性，就像某种意义上的变化
Not really qualitative , like change in a way
所以我想在工作室
So i think at the studio
这对我们有好处
It was good for us
呃
Uh
所以就像现在尝试一些东西
So just like now try something
你知道，做点别的事，比如开发，呃
You know , do something else , like develop , uh
你知道，尝试一下
You know , try to
是的
Yeah
第一次做某事
Do something for the first time
而不是停留在同一个公式中，呃
Instead of staying in the same formula , uh
但其实没那么重要
But it's actually less important
我认为更重要的永远是
I think the more important is always like
您尝试将形式与功能相匹配
You try to match the form with the function
嗯，在某种程度上
Um , in a way
还有，嗯，赛博朋克
And , um , cyber punk
实际上我们可以像我一样破坏一下游戏吗
And actually can we spoil the game a little bit like i
我们不会玩任务
We won't be playing quest
但只有一点点剧透
But just a little bit of spoilers
没关系
It's fine
我正值那个时候
I'm time of that
是的
Yeah
嗯，对吧
Um , right
所以在比赛的第一个大转折点
So at the first big turning point of the game
事实证明，你不仅快要死了，而且很快就会死
Like it turns out that not only you are dying and you will die soon
但你脑子里也有另一个人
But also you have this other person in your head
而这两种经历
And both of those experiences
让我们说一下，呃，类似的经历，呃
Let's say the , uh , experience of like , uh
你的身体有些腐烂
Your body decaying somewhat
就像，你知道，你被困在身体里的死亡，呃
And like , you know , the mortality of the body you are trapped inside , uh
还有超主观的
As well as the super subjective
想象一下看到你身边的另一个人
Think of like seeing that other person in your
呃，在你的脑海里
Uh , in your head
这是一个非常主观的事情，fbp 觉得讲述一个非常主观的事情是正确的选择
It's something that is so subjective that fbp felt like the right choice to tell a very
非常主观的故事
Very subjective story
另外，呃
And in addition , uh
我认为有类似的比喻，嗯，嗯，嗯
I think there's like trope , um , of , um
这与像这个凡人监狱一样的身体和技术的网络朋克一起工作，作为一种喜欢的方式
That works with cyber punk of like body as this smortal prison and technology as a way to like
你知道，释放你自己或者以某种方式同意，你知道，这个，这个，这个身体
You know , free yourself or somehow assent from , you know , this , this , this body
这也适用于 , 对于游戏
And this also works like for , for the game
现在如果你有 fbp
And now if you would have fbp
这将与第三人称场景混合在一起
That would be mixed with third person scenes
它并没有真正给你
It kind of doesn't really give you
这种感觉就像被囚禁一样，你无法真正摆脱它
This feeling of like imprisonment in a way that you cannot really get out of it
就好像是的
It's like yeah
你被困在他的身体里
You are trapped in his body
死亡等
Dying and so on
但这实际上就像是别人的外部观点
But here is like an external point of view actually of someone else
喜欢第三人称场景
Like the third person scene
它会像这样工作
It would work like this
它是
It's
是的
Yeah
外面还有
There's the outside
也许她看到了更悲伤的角色
And maybe she sees the sader character
但作为相机我是谁
But who am i done as a camera
喜欢从什么角度看
like from what perspective
我正在看这个。等等
I am watching this . and so on
所以对于这个故事来说，这感觉是一个非常正确的选择
So it felt like a really right choice for this exact story
嗯
是的
Yeah
我想，呃，这就是我的解释
That would be , i think , uh , my explanation
因为到最后
Because at the end of the day
我们想讲最好的故事，对吗？
We want to tell the best stories , right
我们通常会根据想要讲述的故事来选择工具
And often we pick the tools based on the stories want to tell
就像你的设定一样
So like in your set
我们非常想告诉这个，呃
We want to tell this very , uh
关于我们扮演的人是谁的主观故事。到底
Subjective story about who the person that we are playing is . in the end
我们可以在游戏一开始就定义它们
We can define , define them at the very beginning of the game somewhat
但我们有一个非常特别的故事要讲
But we have a very particular story to tell
我们认为这是真正实现这一目标的最佳方式，对吗？
And we felt that this is the best way to actually approach it , right
拥有如此多的互动性
To have this amount of interactivity
不仅在世界上
Not only in the world
但也从演示的角度来看
But also from the presentation standpoint
因为到最后
Because at the end of the day
当你确实有一些东西离相机很近时，你就可以
When you actually have something very close to the camera , you well
你可以看到最好的
You can see the best you can
你可以，你可以体验这个亲密小故事的最好版本
You can , you can experience the best possible version of this small intimate story
呃
Uh
所以我想注意
So i would like to note
注意一些狂野的，呃
Note some the wild , uh
第二次前实际上是在和詹金斯交谈
Second ago was actually talking with jenkins
我想指出的是，jenki 的头部是按照 eager 建模的
And i would like to note that jenki's head was modeled after eager
所以你实际上有正确的 h
So you actually have the correct h
不不不，那是，正在通话中
No , no , that was , that was on the call
正在通话中
It was on the call
为什么你会在一分钟后在现实生活中与你交谈
Why it you're you're gonna talk to in real life in a minute
是的
Yeah
因为他和你有过一次全息手术
Because he had a holocaular with with you
哦，这
Oh thris
是的
Yeah
一
Um
所以，你知道，网络故事
So , you know , internet story
正如你所看到的，就像
And as you can see , like the
，视角的接近性在这里有帮助
The , the closeness of the perspective helps here
正确的
Right
嗯嗯
Uh huh
出色地
Well
你知道，我在想我们正在看哪三个
You know , i was thinking about we were watching which are three
你知道，迈克尔对所有这些技术都很熟悉
You know , i all those technies are so familiar to michael
而我作为有电影背景的人
And i as people with a film background
你知道这个，哦，这是一个移动镜头，这是一个从肩膀上反向拍摄的镜头
You know this , oh , it's a dolly shot here's this shot reverse shot over the shoulder
这让我觉得这是虚拟现实的语言
And this strikes me as the language of virtual reality
这是，这是你们几乎要致力于一件事
This is , this is you guys are committing almost to a thing
这只有在虚拟中才有可能，嗯
That is only possible in that virtual , um
第一人称视角空间
First person perspective space
所以你在某种程度上做出了可能喜欢的贡献
so you're kind of contributing in a way to like potentially
随着虚拟现实变得越来越多，我们将探索一种未来的电影语言
A future cinematic language that we're gonna be exploring as virtual reality becomes more and more
呃
Uh
你知道，这是一种通用的讲故事方式
You know , a universal kind of way to tell stories
嗯，你确实触及了一个巨大的话题
Well , you touched upon gigantic subject that's for sure
我们可能只能谈论一个小时
We could probably talk about an hour only about this
因为我同意你的观点
Because i agree with you
我们正处于这中间的某个地方
We are somewhere in the middle of this
你知道，完全虚拟现实体验
You know , fully vr experience
还有这种经典的电影体验，对吧
And this classical cinematic experience , right
因为我们实际上只是介于两者之间
Because we actually are but kind of in the between of them
一
Um
当我们开始研究弗兰克说时
And when we started working on sayer frank
我们分析了过去二十年的第一人称游戏体验
We analyzed the last twenty years of first person experiences in games
我们知道，我们研究了一些有效的方法和一些无效的方法
And we know we , we looked at some things that worked and someone that didn't
我们最终得出了这个独特的结论
And we ended up in this unique take
我觉得这实际上同时推动了多个方向的界限
I feel that actually pushes the boundaries in multiple directions at once
因为但最终
Because but at the end of the day
我们在这里以前所未有的方式命名未知领域
We are naming uncharted territors here , like no one
我我我不知道其他设计实际上采用了这个
I , i , i don't know other design actually took this
整个故事的这种处理方式就像完整的故事结束了，你知道，二十，四十
This approach to the whole like full blown story over , you know , twenty , forty
在这里可以实际体验的五十个小时
Fifty hours that you can actually experience here
这实际上具有极高的分支保真度
That actually has branching extremely high fidelity
可定制的角色
Customizable characters
啊，这是，这是一个非常复杂的想法
Ah , it's , it's a very complex idea
但最后我觉得是的
But in the end , i feel that yeah
我们实际上在这里做了一些非常特别的事情
We actually done something very special here
一
Um
是的
Yeah
我喜欢看比赛
I like i'm looking at the game
因为我真的很想开始谈论游戏了
Because i really want to start talking about the game already
就像很多事情一样，比如过去的事情
Like so many things like when went past , for example
我们如何从特写镜头开始
How we start with a close up shot
呃
Uh
感觉真的很像
Which felt was really like
呃，对我们有感觉
Uh , felt for us
与你的角色建立这种个人联系非常重要
Was really important to set up this personal connection with your character
在游戏中更是如此
Even more so in a game that's about
就像你定制你的角色一样
Like you customize your character
然后你就可以在游戏中真正看到这个角色并说
And then you can really see this character during the game and say
来吧，就像我们说的那样
Come on , like let's say remark
我们上网
We get on the , on the internet
所以至少在一开始就以某种方式将你与这个，呃，角色联系起来
So at least at the beginning to tie you somehow with this , uh , character
而且它的工作原理就像是在相对括号中说的
And also it works is like it let's say in a rative bracket
因为游戏是从穿上衣服开始的
Because the game starts with the clothes up
最后把衣服穿好，呃，还有
And ends with the clothes up , uh , as well
就像一种类似的封闭
Just as a kind of like closure to the
嗯，讲故事吧，嗯
Um , to the story , um
无论如何，嗯，就喜欢而言
Anyway , um , in terms of like
也许让我们更详细地了解我们如何处理这个问题
Maybe let's go into more details about how we approach this
例如，一件事
so for example , one thing
我想我希望场景中已经能感受到这一点
and i think i hope it can be already felt in the scene
现在玩的时候
While playing right now
我们的基本假设之一是我们希望玩家成为场景中的演员
Is one of our base assumptions was that we want the player to be an actor in a scene
实际上并不喜欢重播其他角色
And not actually like replaying other character
尽管 。当然你总是有限制的
Though . of course you always have limits of
您可以允许玩家做什么
What you can like allow player to do of
因为很多原因
Because of many reasons
就像，你知道，制作以及我们想要如何推动故事一样
Just like , you know , production and how we want to drive the story
一
Um
但我们一直想要，呃
But we always wanted to the , uh
扮演场景中呃，呃，演员的玩家
The player to be the u , uh , actor in the scene
所以让玩家在场景中实际做事而不是观看它们
So for the player to actually do things in the scene instead of watching them
所以我们是故意的，例如这里
So we on purpose , for example here
就像詹金斯从办公桌上站起来走到另一个地方时一样
Like when jenkins gets up from his desk and walks to another place
我们想向您展示，在此期间苏也移动
We want to show you that during this su also move
你实际上可以进行这样的对话
and you could actually have this conversation
而依然坐在书桌旁的椅子上。这是你的选择
While still sitting on the chair by the desk . it's your choice
就像你可以这样表达自己
Like you can express yourself be this
你知道，就像听话的人对某件事有联系一样
You know , like obedient persons being connectary as about something
一些事情，或者像和他一起散步并尝试成为更多的合作伙伴等等
Something , or like walk with him and try to maybe be more of a partner and so on
当然，大家始终与他同行
Of course , everybody always walks with him
因为这是最吸引人的内容
Because it's the most attractive content
比方说，嗯
Let's say , um
所以这是一回事
So this was one thing
其次，我们一直想为玩家提供
And second , we always wanted to give players
在任何特定时刻都有尽可能多的自由
As much freedom as possible at any given moment
就像我们总是问我们一些事情
Like we're always asking us stuff
好的
Okay
我们现在能给玩家更多的自由吗？
Can we give player more freedom in this moment that we are giving him right now
当然你不能总是这样做
And of course you cannot always do this
因为有时你有一个非常精确的信息需要吸引玩家的注意力
Because sometimes you have a very precise information that you need to focus player's attention on
嗯，为了让他不要让他们分心
Um , for him not to get for them to not get distracted
如果玩家途中分心
If the player gets distracted by the way
他指责比赛不给他机会
He blames the game for like not giving him
这些信息足够好，而不是像存在，哦耶
The information well enough instead of like being , oh yeah
也许应该，也许我应该更多
Should maybe , maybe i should have be more
你知道，以后要小心
You know , careful the back then
现在这样不行了
Now it doesn't work this way
一
Um
所以有时候是故意的
So sometimes on purpose
我们像某处所说的那样培养收藏家
We make collectors like said somewhere
或者，你知道，就像靠在某个东西上，让你的注意力集中在与你交谈的其他角色上
Or , you know , like lean on something to just focus you on other character talking to you
但即便如此，我们仍然想给你
But even then we want to like give you still the
呃，相机自由度，呃，运动
Uh , camera of the freedom of camera , uh , movement
但那里，呃，甚至像这里这样的场景
But there , uh , even the scenes like here
比如说，和你喜欢的这个助手一起去
For example , with this assistant that you just like went
例如，从他身边经过
Went past him , for example
从我们的角度来看这不是一个超级重要的场景
It's not a super important scene from our perspective
就像是一团绒毛
Like it's a fluff
所以基本上我们可以在这里为您提供更多的自由
So basically we can provide you more freedom here
这取决于你想不想和他说话
It's up to you want to talk with him
你想要旋转并站在他身后
you want to like rotate and stand behind him
然后他就会轮流转向你
And he rotates to you
他是否轮换并不重要
It doesn't really matter if he's rotated or not
因为后台启动那件事很重要
Because the background is started that thing important
如果这是一个主线故事的话
If though it would be a main story
告诉你，电脑是非常非常重要的东西
And pc was something really , really important to tell you
例如，我们可能不知道他会抓住你
We would probably i don't know he would catch you for example
或者他会说，来吧
Or he would be like , come on
让我们在这里停留一会儿
Let's stay here for a little moment
我需要告诉你更多的事情
I need to tell you something more
等等
And so on
所以我们知道他所关注的球员就像
So just the player we know that he's focused on like
我们在 daan 特定时刻呈现的内容
What we are presenting at daan given moment
所以我们经常谈论
So we are often talking about
关于噪声和信号关于我们需要始终理解的这个想法
about noise and signal about this idea that we need to always understand
最重要的信息想传达给玩家什么
What the most important information want to convey to the player
正确的
Right
是我们希望玩家体验的实际内容
Was the actual thing that we want the player to experience
去感受、去理解
To feel , to to understand
当这一幕真实发生后
After the scene actually happened
呃
Uh
我们有多种方式引导玩家放弃这种体验
And we have multiple ways to guide the player drop this experience
呃，就像你那套里的一样
Uh , like in your set
人们坐下，人们走开
People sitting down , people walking away
玩家处于封闭空间
Player being in a closed space
玩家输入av ，就像在这个例子中一样，对吧
Player entering av , like in this case , right
呃，这些其实都是我们整个游戏过程中可以用到的工具
Uh , all of those are actually the tools that we can use during the whole game
这以一种希望无缝的方式融合了旁白和游戏玩法
And that blend the narration and gameplay in a way that's hopefully seamless
我，我认为在大多数情况下都是这样
And i , i think in this case for most of the time
我们实际上成功了，呃
We actually succeeded in that , uh
而你享受
And you enjoy
而且，你知道，你，你，你在整个体验过程中都在玩
And , you know , and you , you , you play throughout the experience
但实际上从来没有，呃
But there's never actually , uh
在旁白部分和游戏部分之间切换
Cut between the narration part and the gameplay part
就像我们看到的，就像我们在猎魔人，呃，片段中看到的那样
Like we watched , like we saw in the , in the witcher , uh , fragment
两者之间有明显的区别，对吗？
There is a clear separation between one and the other , right
在这个游戏中，在这个非常特别的游戏中
And in this game , in this very particular game
没有
There is none
我们想要推动这种程度的自由
We wanted to push this amount of freedom
我们可以给玩家尽可能多的
We can give the player as much as possible
当它仍在交付时，重视一个想要讲述的非常特别的故事
While it's still deliving , valuvering a very particular story that want to tell
因为在一天结束时
Because at the very end of the day
我们是学习者，对吧
We are study tters , right
我们，我们想讲述这个故事
We , we want to deliver this story
我们想要创造的这种激动人心的东西
This emotional gut punching thing that we want to create
并想让玩家体验火爆
And want to player to experience hot
是的
Yeah
一，一
Um , um
是的
Yeah
我会
I will
所以是的
So yeah
我感觉里面有很多东西
I feel like there's so much in , in there
所以，听起来你们很像
And so it , it sounds like you guys
你是在谈论一个，呃
Are you're kind of talking about a , uh
一种控制方式
A way of controlling
一
Um
或者建议喜欢玩家关注
Or suggesting like player attention
或者就像在某些不那么重要的时刻
Or like in some moments where it's less critical
他们有更多的自由
They have more freedom
所以如果他们错过了也没关系
So if they miss it , it's fine
但在类似故事的关键时刻
But in like story critical moments
您可以掌控一切以确保人们不会错过它
You are able to like take control to make sure people don't miss it
而且，就像你说的，你知道
And , and also like you're saying , you know
从游戏玩法到电影的无缝过渡
The seamlessness of moving from gameplay to cinematics
你知道，我，我想我很早就记得了
You know , i , i think i remember early on
呃，保罗，你和我就像在推特上聊天一样
Uh , paul , you and i were like chatting on twitter
还有一场关于电影艺术的对话
And there was a conversation about cinematics
我当时想，等等
And i was like , wait
这游戏有动画吗
Are there cinematics in this game
因为它，感觉不像传统的电影理念
Because it , it doesn't feel like the conventional like idea of cinematics
所以我想，我认为你们一定能实现这一点
And so i think , i think you guys definitely achieve that
因为我的大脑必须喜欢处理类似的事情，好吧
Because it my brain had to like process that of like , all right
就像这些算作电影，因为它是讲故事的
Like these count as cinematics because it's storytelling
但在第一人称视角下却是如此无缝
But it is so seamless in that first person perspective
你可以在办公室里跑来跑去
Where you can be running around the office
现在你在这辆车里
And now you're in this car
呃，你知道，飞行汽车avv，对吧
Uh , you know , the the flying car avv , right
是的
Yeah
AV，呃，啊，参加这个很棒的巡演
Av , uh , ah , getting this awesome tour
而且是如此天衣无缝
And it is so seamless
一
Um
我只是觉得这是一件非常令人印象深刻的事情
I just think that's a really impressive thing
我觉得
And i feel like the
汽车修理工是对我来说最突出的事情之一
the car mechanics is one of the things that stood out to me
作为，作为有时的例子，呃
As , as an example of sometimes when , uh
你就像接到某人的任务
You're like getting a mission from someone
你走，你坐在车里
You go and you sit in the car
然后你就不能走动了
And then you can't move around
所以你有点被迫，呃
So you're sort of forced to , uh
以某种方式聆听该玩家的声音
Listen to that player in a way
这仍然让人感觉身临其境且真实
That still feels immersive and true to the world
所以，是的
So , yeah
你们还用过其他一些技巧吗？
Where there's some other techniques you guys used to , uh
在需要时吸引玩家的注意力
Draw player attention when you needed to
嗯，有很多这样的
Well , there are like so many
我们甚至可以停下来，呃
And we could like even stop , uh
不知道下一个场景
I don't know at the next scene
我们可以谈谈这个
And we can talk about this
我的意思是，有些比较复杂，有些则比较简单
I mean , some of them are more complex , sometimes less
但是，嗯，呃，有人可能会在这一点上发表评论
But , um , uh , one may remark at this point
我，我认为这是游戏制作过程中的一个有趣的发现
Which i , i think was like an interesting discovery during the making of the game
就像一开始一样，这整个就像我喜欢太阳能fpp的想法
Like at the beginning , this whole like i like solar fpp idea
或者在整个游戏过程中
Or throughout the game
就像工作室里很多人并不买账一样
Like many people at the studio didn't really buy it
或者你没有真正明白或喜欢
Or didn't you they really get it or like
但你要如何讲述此时此刻
But how are you going to tell this moment or this moment
就像这怎么可能
Like how's it possible
当然你需要喜欢做特写
Of course you need to like do a close up
你知道，插话什么的
You know , cut in or something
一
Um
而且，呃，实际上我们非常关心，好吧
And , uh , actually we were pretty concerned with like , okay
我们给予玩家自由
We give players freedom
所以他们会喜欢在我们重要的场景中
So they will just like in the middle of our important scene
他们会转身走开
They will turn around and walk away
就像我的故事等等
And like what with my story and so on
而实际上
And actually
事实证明，对于 98% 的玩家来说
And it turns out that for ninety eight percent of players
人们只是想玩游戏
People just want to play the game
这很像一个简单的想法
It's a very like a simple maybe thought
但这对我们来说至关重要
But it's a crucial for us
因此，人们通常希望您能够为他们提供最具吸引力的内容
So people usually they want the most attractive content you can provide them with
如果他们有像超有吸引力的NPC
If they have like the super attractive npc
同样很酷的东西和移动可以令人印象深刻并且喜欢尝试
Same cool stuff and moving can immating and like trying to
你知道，与他们有联系等等
You know , relate to them and so on
就像他们为什么会选择看人行道一样
Like why would they choose looking at the sidewalk
或者就像在这个特定的时刻走开
Or like walking away at this given moment
就像一开始我们在想
And like at the beginning we were thinking
哦，我们需要确保所有员工的安全，需要所有这些围栏系统等等
Oh , we'll need to secure all the staff would like all those fence systems and so on
然后当你喜欢在youtube上观看《rust》时，人们就会准确地玩
And then when you like watch play rust on youtube , people play exactly
他们希望他们像我们希望他们那样打球
They want they like the way we want them to play
即使他们可以打破比赛
Even though they could break the game
就像在很多不同的场合走开一样
Just by like walking away at so many different occasions
一
Um
例如，也许实际上不在此处的产品中，或者为什么在此处
Maybe not in the product actually here or why at this , for example
这是游戏的开头
This is opening of of of the game
我们不想让玩家离开去参观整个城市
We didn't want the players to leave to like visit the whole city
所以在你的一系列类似的有限香料中
So here in your in a series of like limited spices
但是当你到达你的时候
But when you get to the u
主要主线剧情，你有这个，我不认识npc
Main main story , you have this , i don't know npc
你知道，你在某个地方遇见了巴拿马
You meet , you know , panam somewhere
就像在他们的谈话中
And like in the middle of their conversation
你可以转身走开，两个月后再回去
You could just like turn around and walk away and go back after two months
就像接听谈话一样
And just like pick up on the conversation
事实证明几乎没有人这样做过
Turns out almost no one does it ever
所以实际上我们可以允许自己提供更多的自由
So actually we could allow ourselves to like provide more freedom
明知道无论如何人们都不会接受
Knowing that people won't take it anyway
但就像感觉会存在一样
But like the feeling will be there
哦，我可以做到这一点
Oh , i could do this
这太酷了
This is so cool
但就像，但你不会对
But like , but you won't right
因为这是你知道的、迷人的幻想在跟你说话
Because here's the you know , attractive fantasy talking to you
我认为迈克尔之前所说的关于整个体验的无缝性很重要
I think it's important what you michael said before about the seamlessness of the whole experience
因为对我来说，就像电影中好的剪辑基本上是玩家看不见的一样
Because for me , just like a good edit in a movie is basically invisible to the player
我感觉到我们传递这些重要内容的方式
i feel the way that we deliver those important
不太重要的故事节拍也应该以同样的方式对玩家不可见
And less important story beats should be invisible to the player in the same way
他们甚至不应该明白
They should not even understand that
哦，这个有点多了
Oh , this is something a bit more
你知道，最好知道
You know , be better to know
内部保真度更高，对吧
Have more fidelity inside , right
而这部分其实不太重要
And this part is actually less important
但是，对于玩家来说，最终的体验应该还是非常相似的
But the , the the experience should still be very much the same for the player in the end
我再次觉得网络PK做得很好
And i feel again that it it's something that cyber pk does pretty well
所以我不知道你现在是否想谈论这个
So i know not if you want to talk about this right now
但是，呃，我们基本上把整个叙述分成了非常具体的部分
But , uh , we basically divided the whole narration into very specific parts
我们决定的地方
Where we decide
好的
Okay
这是祈祷需要有很大自由的部分
This is the part where the prayer needs to have a lot of freedom
这实际上是我们最想提供的自由的部分
And this is the part where actually the freedom that that we want to deliver the most
这是最有力的叙述，对吧
That the most punchy amount of narration possible , right
所以我们称它们为眼泪
So we call them tears
所以我们从一到五
So we have teers through one to five
第一个是完全游戏
And the first one is fully game play
第五部基本都是过场动画
The fifth is basically fully cutscene
现在我们就在中间
And right now we are straight in the middle
所以这是第三层，玩家实际上坐下来
So this is the third tier where players actually sitting down
而且它对相机的控制非常有限
And it has very limited control of the camera
但这使我们能够提供特定的内容
But this allows us to deliver specific content
这使得我们可以拥有内部没有摄像头的相机，对吧
This allows us to have camera without cameras inside , right
我们，我们，我们也许有相同的工具
We , we do , we have the same tools maybe
但我们仍然没有这样的削减
But still we don't have the cut that would
这在电影中是找不到的
That would not about be found in a movie
实际上你可以在这里看到，嗯
And actually you can see here , um
基本上这对杰基来说是一个中景，对吧
Basically what's this a medium shot towards to jackie , right
如果他真的对我们有意
And if he actually means towards us
我们突然把衣服脱光了
We have clothes up suddenly
如果他站起来并真的走开
If he gets up and actually walk away
我们还有更多东西
We have something more
这样我们就可以充分利用现有的内容
So we can play a lot with the content that we have
即使玩家可能根本不明白发生了什么
Even though the player might not even understand what's happened
因为他想坐下来
Because he wanted to sit down
因为游戏，你知道，收获
Because the game , you know , the gain
游戏提供了坐下的选项，这是这次转换对话中最吸引人的部分，对吗？
The game presented the options to sit down as the most attractive part of this convert conversation , right
因为他邀请我们参与对话
Because he invites us towards the conversation
有人玩家，玩家认为，好吧
And somebody player , player thinks , okay
是的
Yeah
当然
Sure
绝对地
Absolutely
我会加入你
I will join you
呃，坐下
Uh , and sit down
我们会一起喝一杯
And we'll have a drink together
尽管这正是我们希望他们做的
Even though this is exactly what we wanted them to
去感受你
To , to feel you
玩这款游戏时真正让我印象深刻的一件事是，你知道，我自己也是一名电影制片人
One thing that really struck me playing the game was , you know , as a filmmaker myself
我不再只是世界上的一名演员
I was getting to be not just an actor in the world
但作为一名电影摄影师
But a cinematographer
你知道，我，我被赋予了创建自己的框架的自由
you know , i , i was given the freedom to create my own frames
并选择我想要的框架在任何特定时刻的样子
And to choose what i wanted my frame to be in any given moment
这是一次非常有趣的经历，是的
And it was a really interesting experience where , yeah
有时我会使用该按钮稍微放大一点，使其更近一些
Sometimes i would use that button to kind of zoom in a bit to just make it a little bit more close up
是的
Yeah
或者，或者，或者，或者有时候我会的，你知道的
Or , or , or , or sometimes i would , you know
我希望你能移动，这样，你知道，这个角色
I would you move so that , you know , the character
我说话的对象就在画面的一角
I was talking to was like just on the corner of the frame
但你知道，这主要是一个
But it was mostly , you know , a
他们身后的风景
A landscape behind them
这真是一次全新的体验
And that was just a really new experience
就像我几乎被邀请去的地方
Where like i was invited almost to
为了帮助以大多数游戏的方式拍摄这部电影
To help shoot this movie in a way that most games
你知道，你们完全可以控制每一帧的样子
You know , you guys are completely in control of , of what each frame looks like
呃，我是说
Uh , i mean
是的
Yeah
嗯，呃
Um , uh
是的
Yeah
当然
Sure
呃
Uh
并且，呃，例如，在那些没有鹿的场景中
And , uh , for example , in those like deer free scenes
我们现在在哪里
Where were where we are u right now
就像相机的旋转一样
It's just like the rotation of the camera
但有很多对一和二，两个场景
But there are like many to one and two , two scenes
您可以在场景中自由移动
Where you can just move freely around the scene
尽管你几乎可以在每个场景中飞来飞去
And even though you can move fly around for almost each scene
我们试图创造一种我们称之为“最佳点”的东西
We tried to create something that we call the sweet spot
就像这样将人物、元素和生活在画面中上演
Which is like this kind of like staging of characters and elements and life in the frame
那种喜欢潜意识里让你站在一个特定的点上
That kind of like subconsciously makes you stand in a specific point
就像你那样做
And like you kind of just do it
对我们来说，这正是重点
And for us , this is the exact point
我们希望你站在哪里
Where we want want you to stand
因为例如这里的背景
Because for example here the background
它的作用就像更好的构图
It works for like a better composition
或者喜欢它以某种方式增加了民主党呃
Or like it somehow adds to the dem uh
或者像增强故事联系一样。等等
Or like enhances the story tying . and so on
通常它就像将角色放置在哪里一样简单
And usually it's as simple as just like placing the character like where
npc的正面在哪里
Where is the front of the npc
通常人们会站在npc的正前方
Usually people will stand right in front of the npc
所以在这里我们知道
So here we know
但我们也可以尝试限制空间
But we can also try to limit the space
身体上有一些资产，比如夏天等等
Physically with some like assets , summer and so on
所以就像，是的，这是npc的正面
So like , yeah , here's the front of npc
但我们被封锁在这里
But we are blocked here
所以实际上你会站到左边一点
So actually you will stand a little bit to the left
呵呵，然后就会有不喜欢的酷
Oh , and then there will be dislike cool
你知道，画面的深度什么的
You know , depth in the frame or something
你可以，嗯，使用，呃
You can , um , use , uh
也喜欢小细节
Also like small details
例如，在地面上
For example , on the ground
有时我知道你有电缆
Sometimes i know you have cables
他们有点像这样
And they kind of make like this
我在某种程度上不了解这个地区
I don't know this area in a way
潜意识里你就站在这个区域内
And subconsciously you stand inside this area
如果有闪电
If there's a lightning
在黑暗的地方你不会明白。等等
You don't understand in the dark places . and so on
所以你可以结合很多不同的元素来以某种方式让玩家
So you can combine a lot of those different elements to somehow make the player
你想让他在哪里
Where you want him to be
我们为此拥有的最后一个工具就像
And the last tool we have for this it's like
假设游戏的金属级别是，呃
Let's say on the metal level of the game is , uh
只是设计交互如何呈现给玩家以及会发生什么
Just the design of how the interactions appear to the player and what happens
所以你可以，例如
So you could , for example
尝试测试一下你什么时候看到对话选项出现
Try to test when do you see the dialogue choices appearing
你离一个角色有多远
How far you are away from a character
因此您无法单击以下选项
So you cannot click the choices from
你知道，有很多摊位
You know , a lot of the stands
因为那时就像这样的电脑
Because then like then pcs like this
有一个，你知道，一个巨大的镜头
There's a , you know , a huge shot
我们不想告诉你一个故事内容
And we don't want to tell you a story content
那里的npc超级超级小
Where like the npc is super , super tiny
所以我们限制了，嗯
So we limited like the the , um
对话选择的范围如何迫使你更加接近
The range of how of where the dialogue choices appear to force you in a way to be closer
但话又说回来，正如pao所说
But again , as pao said
这一切都应该是看不见的
It all should feel invisible
它应该感觉自然并且突出
It should just feel natural and project o
现在我可以说话了
And now i can talk
而且感觉应该是公正的，你知道的
And it should feel just , you know
在某种程度上是正确的
Correct in a way
或者举个例子，明白了，呃
Or for example , understand , uh
每当你选择对话选项时
Whenever you pick a dialogue choice
不看npc
Not looking at the npc
我们会自动将你轮换到npc
We will automatically rotate you to the npc
只是为了确保你不只是像流动员工并在这里的某个地方做出选择
Just to make sure that you are not just like loating staff and taking choices somewhere here
就像忘记这一切一样
And like forgetting about all of this
但实际上在选择的时候
But actually when picking choice
它提醒你，你知道，这是关于故事的
It reminds you , you know , to that it's about story
但同样，大多数时候人们在选择选择时已经在看npc了
But again , most of the time people pick choices while already looking at npc
所以他们并没有真正意识到这个，嗯，效果是一样的
So they don't really perceive this , um , effect that same
这是我们和约翰，呃，还有杰基斯
And here the uswith john , uh , with jackie si
就像想要完成一样
Just like want to finish
我喜欢这个场景，就像舞台的运作方式一样
I like the scene in terms of like how staging works
你走近他，作为欢迎的特写镜头
You approach him as a close up for welcome
然后是中景
Then it's a medium shot
然后你说的话与你相冲突
Then you are saying something that conflicts you
于是他走开了
So he walks away
其他人，请进来
Other guys , guys come in
他们喜欢围绕着你
They like kind of surround you
其中一个人靠得更近了
One of them leans closers
所以这就像是，你知道
So it's like , you know
给你更大的压力然后杰基节省为零
More pressure on your then jackie saves zero
所以有点像再次
So it kind of like again
舞台表演有点倒退
The staging goes a little bit back
最后
And in the end
他再次和你一起在最后为这就像法国前线的时刻换上衣服
He joins you again for a clothes up for this like front to french moment at the very end
所以我们拍摄了一系列的照片
So we had the whole array of shots
虽然实际上几乎没有在镜头前移动
While actually not moving at the camera almost at all
就像以某种方式围绕场景旋转一样
Just like rotating it , you know , around the scene in a way
对不起
Sorry
不
No
我真的很喜欢有这样一种疯狂的内容，我们可以在什么时候谈论
I seriously like there is such an insane breath of content that we can talk about when
每当我们真正看这个游戏时
Whenever we actually look at this game
正确的
Right
这我，我喜欢，我喜欢这个场景
This i , i like , i love this scene
呃，什么，什么急于营救杰基
Uh , what , what eager set about jackie rescue
并猜测此时此刻
And guess in this moment
这一刻我爱他们
I love them this moment
因为当他这样做的时候，声音就会传到你的耳中
Because when he does that , the , the sound comes back to you
突然间，基地实际上受到了更大的打击
Suddenly the , the base actually hits even harder
正确的
Right
而这一切的发生只是因为我们是电影设计师
And this all happens only because we are cinematic designers
呃，一直在和其他团队合作
Uh , are constantly working with other teams
因此，例如，在这种情况下
So , for example , in this case
音频和音乐，呃
The audio and music , uh
你知道，实际上是设计师和创作者
You know , designers and composes actually
我们正在与我们合作，以交付
We're working with us to , to , to deliver
这一刻对玩家来说最好的版本，对吧
The best possible version of this moment to , to , to the player , right
因为这不会在真空中发生
Because this does not happen in a vacuum
就像这一切一样
Like all of this
另外，所有的内容基本上都存在于整个游戏中
In other , all the contents basically exist within the whole game
整个游戏是由很多人创造的
And the whole game is created by a lot of people
呃
Uh
和
And
一方面
And on one hand
你可以说电影设计师实际上正在创造我们可以在这些场景中使用的两个场景
You can say cinematic designers are actually creating that the two sets that we can use in those scenes
但另一方面
But on the other hand
我们都与其他人一起工作
We all work with other people
我们交付，你知道，一些非常非常有趣的东西
And we delivery , you know , some something very , very fun
呃呃，最后
Uh , uh , at the end of it
好的
All , right
进入半年蒙太奇
Onto the half year montage
之后我认为我们进入了最具争议的时刻之一
After which i think we go to at one of the most controversial moments
嗯，在游戏中
Um , in the game
比如说，呃，互联网上有很多人担心它应该可以玩
Let's say , uh , a lot of concerns on the internet that it should have been playable
等等
And so on
我们总是这样思考序列
And we always thought about the sequence as such
我们一直想加快故事的进度
And we always wanted to speed up the story
让我们来谈谈真正重要的是什么
Let's say a little bit to what's really crucial for it
例如，从我的角度来看
And for example , from my perspective
如果我们真的和杰基一起度过这六个月的话，就像结构上的那样
If we really spend those six months here with jackie , like from the structure
屏幕位置结构观点
Screen place structure point of view
假设你就像第一幕一样
Let's say you are in like the first act
事实上甚至在之前，你知道，转折点等等
And actually before even like , you know , the turning point and so on
所以这就像拉伸超长时间一样
So it would be just like stretching it for super long
实际行动从这里开始
And here the actual action starts
它开始一次就像在最高的末尾
And it starts once like at the end of the highest
你知道，当你拿到筹码时，约翰尼·银的手就在你的脑海里
You know , when you get the chip with johny silver hand in your head
就像在这部分扩展游戏一样
So like expanding the game on this part
这对于我们稍后要告诉你的事情来说并不起作用
It doesn't really work for what we want to tell you later
这是关于与约翰尼·尤的个人关系的故事
And it's the story about this personal relationship with johnny yoo
那些其他角色等等
Those other characters and so on
就像和杰基一起在城市里做演出一样
And just like doing gigs with jackie around the city
当然很酷
Sure it's cool
但这非常像开放世界的公式
But it's a very like open world formula
没有特定的角色目标或特定的冲突
Without particular like goal for the character or particular conflict
我就像这个想知道赚钱的人
I'm just like this guy trying to know to earn some money
但一旦我们开始死亡，就不再真正关注它
But there's no real tention to it once we start dying
还有过去的网络恐怖分子
And the cyber terrorists from the past
如你所知，就像在你的脑海里一样
As you know , like in your head
但这就是，你知道，紧张局势产生的地方
But this is where the , you know , the tension arises
我想，对吧
I think , right
一
Um
然而对我来说，这就是，这就是旧世界
Yet to me , this is , this is the old world
你知道，在一个经典的英雄之旅三幕结构中
You know , in a , in a classic hero's journey three act structure
这只是确定旧世界是什么
This is just establishing what the old world is
当你离开旧世界时，故事才真正开始
And the story really gets going when you leave the old worlds
这就是约翰尼银手
And that's the johny silver hand
你知道，遗迹，对吧
You know , relic , right
所以，在这一切之前你确实可以和杰基一起执行一些任务并建立这种关系
So , and you do get to play some missions with jackie before all that and build up that relationship
还有，所以，是的
And , and so , yeah
所以，我们已经完成了公司简介，呃
So , so we've finished the kind of the corpo intro , uh
现在我们要开始抢劫了，呃
And now we are gonna jump to the heist , uh
所以这有点像这种序言介绍的结尾，呃
So this is sort of like at the end of this kind of prologue intro , uh
这一切都是为了这次抢劫任务
It's all building up to this heist mission
超级有趣
Which was super fun
我爱抢劫
I love heists
所以我真的很喜欢玩抢劫，呃
And so i really enjoyed getting to play through a heist , uh
还有所有这些 eb 和流向它
And there's all these ebs and flows to it
而且，我们会看看，嗯
And , and we'll take a look at that , um
但有些事情你们我们是
But kind of some one of the things you guys we're
我们只是说我认为真正有趣的是
We're just saying that i think is really interesting is
你知道你本质上是如何使用字符阻塞的，对吧
You know how you're using essentially character blocking , right
就像场景中演员的移动来创造不同的镜头
Like the movement of the actors in a scene to create different camera
你知道，你知道，特写镜头还是中景镜头
You know , you know , a closeup or a medium shot
那么那些效果
So those effects
但也是剧院的方式
But also the way in theater
当你去看电影或戏剧时，你会使用阻塞
You use blocking where , you know , you go to see a movie or a , a play
以及角色彼此远离或靠近时的动作
And the movement of the characters when they walk away from each other or towards each other
背对着观众
Face the audience face away
就像所有的一切都带有情感
Like all of that has an emotional
呃，意义重大
Uh , significance to it
所以这是一种像戏剧表演阻塞的奇怪混合体
And so it's this kind of weird hybrid of like theatrical play blocking
但仍然需要与相机进行交互
But with a camera that still has to be interacted with
是的
And yeah
我只是好奇，就像那是什么
I'm just curious , like what was that
怎么样，你是怎么想到这个的？
How was , how was it getting your minds around that
就像发现使用角色移动来引导玩家的技术一样
And like discovering those techniques of using character movement to guide a player
这就是情感体验
That's emotional experience at
在某种程度上
At some level
我认为这和经典电影制作是一样的
I think it's the same as in classic film making
这么说吧。所以基本上，就像，如果你减少它
Let's say . so basically , like , if you reduce it
很多都在指导，呃
A lot is guiding , uh
观众的目光扫视屏幕，呃
Viewers eye around the screen , uh
同时向他提供不同的信息
While providing him with different information
并给出了类似的时间跨度，呃，呃
And given like span of time , uh , uh
所以基本上是随着时间的推移构建信息流
So basically a structuring the flow of information through time
呃，就像用冰所感知的那样
Uh , by like perceived with ice moustly
当然，就像，呃
Of course , like , uh
外面也有
Out there as well
一
Um
而且，嗯，这样
And , um , in this way
在某种程度上有点相似
It's kind of similar in a way
所以基本上我们从不希望角色喜欢
So like basically we never , you know , want characters to like
我们不希望屏幕上同时出现太多噪音
We don't want to have too much noise on the screen at the same time
例如
So for example
如果有重要的NPC跟你说话
If you have important npc talking to you
例如，我们会尝试以某种方式
We will try to somehow , for example
降低此时背景传来的噪音，嗯
Reduce the noise coming from the background at this moment , um
只是为了让某人能够，呃，能够专注于，呃，这件事
Just so that someone can , uh , can focus , uh , on this
所有这一切都像测试一样降临到我们身上
And all of this came to us like troud the tests
我想当他们只是在演戏的时候
I think when they were just like playing the scene
我当时，我真的无法集中注意力，好吧
And i was , i cannot focus really like , okay
所以让我们停下来
So let's stop
让我们想想哪里出了问题，背景中的鼻子太多了
Let's think what's wrong there's just too much nose in the background
而我的目光却不断地远离
And my eye constantly keeps getting away from
你知道，就像那里正在发生的事情的面孔
You know , like the face to something that's happening there
所以也许我们可以关闭交通
So maybe let's turn off the traffic
也许我们可以改变光链接的比例
Maybe let's change the ratio of light link
也许让我们稍微旋转一下这个场景
Maybe let's rotate this scene a little bit
就像旋转那些椅子一样。等等
And like rotate those chairs . and so on
所以就像是玛丽一样
So that like it's mari
现在被抑制了，等等
And now subdued and , and so on
所以基本上就是不断地判断，比如你是否分心了
So basically just constantly judging , like are you distracted
或者你正在感知你应该感知的东西
Or are you perceiving what you should be perceiving
当然，就像我们是自己最糟糕的评判者一样
And of course , like we are our own worst judges
我想，也喜欢看别人打球
I think , but also like watching other people play
从工作室周围获取反馈，嗯
Getting feedback from around the studio , um
等等，例如
And so on here , for example
有这样的分期案例
Have this case of staging
确切地
Exactly
所以我们有杰基，他就像一只手
So we have jackie , he's like on one hand
面向你
Facing towards you
而且，嗯，就像九十度一样，以，呃
And , um , like with ninety degrees , staging with the , uh
接待处就像是，你还能站在哪里？
Reception is like , where else could you stand
可能
Possibly
非常确定。你有行动自由
So sure . you have freedom of movement
而且你还可以在这里与一只发光的大手进行互动
And also you have interaction right here with a huge glowing hand
这样你就可以站在杰基后面
So you could stand behind the jackie
但这样的内容吸引力会降低
But like this would be the less attractive content
所以人们想看到面孔
So people want to see faces
他们想看到情感。等等
They want to see emotions . and so on
几乎所有人都站在这里
And almost everyone stands here
然后我们可以强迫你
And then we can force you
就像以某种方式强迫你
Like in a way force you
你，你不会知道的
You , you won't know it
但我们会强迫你，例如
But we will force you just by , for example
将这种推动任务进展的互动放在一个非常特别的聚光灯下
Putting this interaction that progresses the quest in a very particular spotlight here
只有在这里你才能最终压缩手
And only here you compress the hand in the end
你必须在此时结束
You have to end up at this point
你知道，呃
You know , uh
我的意思是，我们生来就具有同理心，对吗？
I mean , we are hard wired towards empathy , right
我们希望人与人之间建立联系
We want the connection between people
我们想要他们之间的互动
We want the interaction between them
所以我们的很多工作都是关于角色，关于那些微小的互动和反应
So a lot of our work is about characters , is about those tiny interactions , reactions
并且，以及人与人之间对话中涉及的一切
And , and everything that goes into conversation between people
我觉得我们从 reer 那里获得了大量的经验
And i feel that we have insane amount of experience from reer
因此，接近这个项目变得容易一些
So approaching this project was a tiny bit easier because of that
因为我们至少知道那部分经历
Because we knew at least that part of the experience
尽管一切都承认它实际上是完全不同的，对吧
Even though everything accept that it was actually completely different , right
而且非常复杂
And it was extremely complicated
呃
Uh
所以我觉得这很有趣
So i think it's interesting
因为我记得人们经常说我们转向第一人称
Because people of i remember people often often said that we move to first person
因为它更容易。因为我们看不到玩家角色
Because it's easier . because we don't see player character
只是那件事
Just the thing
就像你是否会看到复杂性一样
Like if if you would see the amount of complexity
第一人称、交互性和实时性
That first person and interactivity and real time
因为，你知道，你知道，你甚至没有这种奇怪的停顿
Because , you know , you know , you don't even even even have this kind of weird pause
当你选择“不在这里”这样的选择时，对吗？
When you pick choices like not really here , right
就像你周围的世界仍然在做事情一样，呃
Like the the world around you does stuff still , uh
如果你看到我们在《巫师》中的图表
If you would see the graphs that we had in witcher
以及我们在赛博朋克中看到的图表
And the graphs that we have in cyber punk there
不会大十倍吧
No ten times bigger , right
这太疯狂了
And it's it's insane
如果你想想有多少工作
If you think about how much work
你真的需要做吗
Do you need to actually to , to do
为了，为了让这一幕变得简单
To , to make this one simple scene
以让玩家满意的方式工作
Work in a way that satisfying towards the player
是的
Yeah
有些东西是看不见的
And some of the stuff is tinvisible
例如，这里的这个例子，这是一个超级简单的事情
For example , this case right here , it's a super simple thing
你和杰基一起去
You go with jackie
还有一个选项可以进入餐厅
And there's like an option to go into the restaurant
也许和外面的一些人谈谈
And maybe talk with some and pis out there
但就是这样，所以杰基
But there's so , so jackie
你有最高的权利这样做
And you have the highest to do so right
突然间有一个超级简单的事情
Suddenly there's like the super simple bit
我们需要思考，好吧
And we need to think , okay
如果玩家决定留在餐厅怎么办
So what if the player decides to stay in the restaurant
杰基做什么的
What does jackie do
如果玩家决定去电梯怎么办
What if the player decides to go to delevator
立即无视jackie等
Immediately and ignores jackie and so on
好的
Okay
因此，如果玩家站起来与接待处交谈
So if the player stands and talks with the reception is
所以杰基走开或者在餐厅旁边等候
So jackie walk away or like waied by the restaurant
好的
Okay
更简单
It's simpler
所以让他在餐厅等着我们就尝试了一下
So let's leave him waiting by the restaurant and we tried it
玩家走进餐厅，杰基拿着手提箱站在那里
And player goes into restaurant and jackie is just standing there with the suitcase
这让他在某种程度上看起来很傻
And it makes him look silly in a way
就像他有他的呃
Like he has his uh
他没有自己的生活
He doesn't have life on his own
他只是在那里等待玩家等等
He's just like there just for to wait for the player and so on
我们总是希望角色可信
And we always want the characters to be believable
所以在这种情况下杰克就像
So in this case jack is like
我不会等你
I'm not gonna wait for you
我就上楼去，你知道的
I'll just go upstairs and you know
就像当你需要的时候来加入我
Like come join me when you when you have to
然后他就走了，但是一个球员在最后一刻跳进了电梯
And then he goes , but what a player jumps into delevator at the very last moment
因为游戏已经让玩家玷污了餐厅
Because the game already things the player stain the restaurant
所以你需要保护所有这些情况
So you need to like secure all those situations
而从玩家的角度来看
And from the player perspective
每个变体都必须可信
Each of those variants needs to be believable
节奏很好
Well paced
表演得好，需要有道理。等等
Well acted , needs to make sense . and so on
还有一千个时刻
And there's a thousand moments
从玩家的角度来看
Which like from the player perspective
噢，在这个空间里感觉很对劲
Oh , it just felt right in this space
但就像你决定与南方精神病患者交谈五分钟一样
But like if you would decide to talk with the southern psy for five minutes
再多五秒钟，就会发生其他事情
Five seconds longer , something else would happen
这对你来说也是很自然的事
And that was also good natural for you
但你实际上从未看到分支
But you never see the branching actually
所以是的，那些走进餐厅的人
So yeah , people who go into the restaurant
杰基就上楼去了
Jackie just goes upstairs there
立即走向电梯的人
People who go immediately to the elevator
杰基和他们一起去，没有说什么
Jackie goes with them and doesn't say some things
因为这就像，你知道，不同的流程穿过，嗯，穿过场景
Because this is like , you know , different flow through the , um , through the scene
我认为这很重要。急切地说了什么，呃
I think it's in , in , in it's important . what eager said , uh
我之前考虑过迭代的数量
i think before about the amount of iterations that
我们必须在非常基本的系统级别上做
We had to do on the very basic system level
例如
So for example
您渴望设置的距离，以进行交互，对吧
The what you eager set about the distance to , to , for interactions , right
例如
So for example
有时，交互实际上与其他地方的人相距很远，例如
Sometimes the interaction is actually pretty far away from the person in other places is actually very closed by for example
我记得有一天晚上，我们花了几个小时只迭代
I remember one evening when , when we spent hours iterating only on
到农作物需要多远的距离
How much distance do we need to have to crops
所以，你知道，做一些事情，例如，在桌子上，呃
So , you know , to do things , for example , on the table , uh
您需要以什么角度与他们进行互动
And what exact angle do you need to have to make the interactions with them
恰到好处，你知道，感觉很好，对吧
Just right , you know , feel properly , right
喜欢，喜欢，喜欢应该有的感觉
Like , like , like it should feel
是的
Yeah
因为如果玩家从极端距离和极端角度点击它
Because if player clicks it from the extreme distance and extreme angles
你就像这片森林一样非常奇怪的混合
And you have like this woods really weird blending
突然感觉它不再是一个身体了
And suddenly it doesn't feel like it's a body anymore
我们之前讨论过的事情
The thing that we talked about before
对我们来说创造你始终在身体内的东西是多么重要啊
How important it was for us to create this thing that you are inside the body at all times , uh
突然感觉很机械化
And suddenly it feels very mechanning
所以是的
So yeah
我们还需要调整很多不同的
We need to like also adjust a lot of different
Like 参数，表示事物在什么情况下如何被触发
Like parameters of how like things get triggered when
所以，呃，一旦你看到某样东西，很多事情就会被触发
So , uh , a lot of things get trigger once you look at something
或者当你进入某个空间或者某个触发器时
Or when you enter a certain space or a certain trigger
再说一遍，这是关于思考的
So again , it's about thinking like
好的
Okay
如果玩家正好处于这个位置
If the player will be in this exact spot
还有什么在争夺他的注意力
What else is fighting for his attention
好的
Okay
不多
Not much
所以也许我们应该从 npc 触发这条线
So maybe we should trigger this line from npc
嘿
Hey
任何
Whatever
此刻来到这里
Come here at this moment
如果还是有太多来自不同方面的刺激
If there's still like too much stimuli coming from different sides
也许你应该稍后触发这个时间
Maybe you should trigger this time a little bit later
当你深入房间时
When you are deeper in the room
周围的噪音又减少了，嗯
And there's like again , less noise around , um
呃，这里，嗯
Uh , here , um
我我我愿意
I , i , i would like to
也许是因为至少要谈论一下同时进行的游戏
Maybe because also to talk at least a little bit about the game that's being played at the same time
而且不仅仅是将军
And not just generals
两者，嗯，与身体不同
Both , um , distinct with body
嗯，这对我们来说也是一个大话题
Um , it was also a big topic for us
所以我设置了关于 fdp 方法的事情
So this thing i set about fdp approach
但我们所说的身体存在对我们来说也非常重要
But also the thing we called body presence in general was super important for us
不仅仅是从讲故事的角度来看,嗯
Not only from storytelling point of view , um
但它也对这种身处世界的感觉产生了很大的束缚
But also it tighed a lot to this kind of feeling of being inside the world
所以你可以在很多很多不同的场合看到v的身影
So you can see at many , many different occasions that you will see glimpses of body of v
例如
So for example
你坐过的每部动画
Every animation you sit on
你在场景中的某个地方被挡住了
And you get blocked somewhere in the scene
你总是看到相机有点下降
You always see like the camera goes a little bit down
你看到腿了
You see the legs
你知道，就像坐下来
You know , like sitting down
然后它又恢复了
And then it goes back up again
所以你总是有上下文
So you always have context
你的身体发生了什么
What is happening with your body
实际上，例如，所有亲爱的免费场景
Actually , for example , all the dear free scenes
当你靠在某物上并且可以自由拍摄时
The one when you sert or lean on something and you have freedom of camera
我们总是离开相机的自由
We always left the freedom of cameras
所以只要你能看到你的身体发生了什么就足够了
So it's enough that you can see what's happening with your body
因为我们在某些迭代中有类似的东西，但我们没有
Because we had like at some iterations , we didn't have it
感觉超级奇怪
And it was super weird feeling like
但我这是怎么了
But what's happening with me
为什么我不能动
Why cannot i move
哦，我不能
Oh , i cannot
所以，呃，好吧
So , uh , okay
因为我坐着。好的
Because i'm sitting . okay
现在有道理了
Now it makes sense
突然间你就进入了角色，嗯
And suddenly you're in the character , um
但一直待在体内也需要我们
But staying all the time inside the body also required us
有时尝试想出创造性的解决方案
Sometimes to do like try to think of creative solutions
如何逃离这个身体
How to escape this body
但总是
But always
呃，就像逻辑这个词一样
Uh , like within the word logic
然后就呆在里面
And staying like , well , um , in inside
你知道，网络朋克的世界
You know , the world of cyber pank
以及技术的运作方式
And the way the technology works
等等，例如，这是其中一个案例
And so on here , here is , for example , one of those cases
呃，就像你在不同的房间里移动蜘蛛机器人一样
Uh , where like you move the spider bot around like different rooms
而且你用相机
And you use cameras
所以实际上你并不在你的身体里
So actually you're not inside your body
现在你有不同的观点
Right now you have different perspective
突然我们在某种程度上添加了，呃
Suddenly we added , uh , in a way
但还是有道理的
But still it makes sense
这不是创作者级别的任意元选择
It's not an arbitrary meta choice from the level of creator
这一切都是按照这个世界的方式来合理的，呃
It's all justified by the way the world does , uh
大脑是，呃，同样的东西
The brain ances is the , uh , the same thing
我们有这样的序列，你扮演约翰，呃
We have this sequences where you play as john , uh
但同样，它发生在
But again , it kind of happens in
这个头实际上就像我们生活在回忆中
And this head actually it's like we're living the memories
部分原因是它实际上是基于像在记忆中潦草地写的那样
And part of it is actually it's really based in like the like scrawling through the memories
这么说吧，好吧
Let's say so , okay
你改变你的身体
You change your body
现在是不同的视角了
It's a different perspective now
但还是有道理的
But still it makes sense
我认为重要的是要注意
I think it's important to note that
在游戏中拥有身体并不是一个显而易见的选择
Having a body inside a game is not really an obvious choice
因为它增加了疯狂的复杂性和直接问题
Because it adds insane amount of complexity and straight up problems
当你想到这一点时
When you think about this
因为到最后
Because at the end of the day
你不是恰好在某个地方的漂浮相机
You are not the floating camera that just happens to be somewhere
你知道，你的身体实际上必须适应这个空间
You actually have the body that has to , you know , fit in the space
必须真正穿过空间
Have to actually move toward through through the space
正确的
Right
我认为我们使用的令人惊奇的调整之一
I think one of the amazing tweaks that we use
也许这是非常罕见的事情
Maybe it's something that's pretty rare
所以基本上我们在相机上有一个视差
So basically we have a parallex on the camera
所以当你真正坐下并旋转相机时
So when you actually sit that and you rotate the camera
这不像愚蠢的 T 部分，只从同一位置旋转相机
This is not like the stupid t section that only rotates the camera from the same spot
你实际上在太空中移动相机
You actually move the the camera in space
所以如果你愿意的话，如果你看看它
So if you will , if you look at it
你会发现事物的位置实际上发生了移动
You will see that the the position of of things actually kind of move
当你轮换时，不同的植物会发生变化
When you rotate the different plants change
因为你还有翻译
Because you have also translation
就像我们的眼睛一样
Just as our eyes
它们的头部并不完全是数学上的零
They are not where the head is exactly such a mathematical zero
你知道，在之前的大部分比赛中
And you know , in most of the previous games
事实上，当你看它的时候
Actually , when you look at it
当你旋转时，你旋转了这个精确的数学点
When you rotate , you rotating this exact mathematical spot
所以背景给人的感觉是，呃，感觉很平坦
So the background it feels , uh , it feels flat
因为在我们的游戏中元素不会在视差中移动
Because the elements don't move in the parallax in our game
当你旋转头部时，即使坐在原位
When you rotate the head even sitting in place
不同的植物会改变它们之间的关系
The different plants will change their like own relationships
因为是的
Because yeah
我们有这样的，甚至这样的设置，u um
We had this and even setting like this , u , um
呃，这个视差弧
Uh , this arc for the parallex
那么相机是如何移动的
So how does the camera move
那么它是这样移动的吗
So does it move like this
还是像这样移动
Or does it move like this
等等本身就像一个挑战
And so on was like a challenge on its own
当感觉就像超级乌戈一样正确时
When it felt right in a way that's like super ugo
是的
Yeah
听到这真是太有根据了
It's so basing to hear about
因为当你玩的时候你会感受到这一切
Because you feel all this when you're playing it
但你不自觉地明白
But you don't consciously understand
为什么你有这样的感觉
Why you feel that way
是的
Yeah
视觉效果很棒，呃，就像《巫师》一样
Great visible , uh , and like just the same way as with witcher
基本上所有的内容和郊区都是完全定制的
Basically all the content and suburbank is completely custom made
它的手手工创建，正确的
Its hand hand created , right
所以哪一年我们有四到五个 Cyber​​pank 设计师
So in which year we had like four to five designers for cyberpank
现在我们有十八个
Right now we have eighteen
以及复杂性和工作量
And the amount of complexity and , and the work
你必须真正做到让这项工作变得疯狂
You have to actually make to make this work is just crazy
但我认为我们是，你知道的
But i think we are , you know
我们正在穿孔，需要几个小时
We are piercing it'll take a couple hours
这里很小，很小，有点疯狂，呃
Tiny , tiny , tiny bit crazy here , uh
因为他们正在做这样的事情，对吧
Because they're doing something like this , right
所以食物长期伴随着身体呈现
So the food long be all the way with body presents with
有阴影，有万物互动
With shadows , with interactions on everything
所以你永远不会真正传送到某个动作之间具有疯狂连续性的地方
So you never actually teleport somewhere with crazy amount of continuity between the action
因为如果我们确实在故事中非常特定的地方进行了编辑
Because if we do have edits there in very particular places in the story
但通常你有这个线性，呃
But normally you have this linear , uh
超高保真解说
Super high fidelity narration
同时
And at the same time
例如，您可以跳过场景之类的事情
You have things like , for example , skipping scenes
哪个存在于世间且不会消失
Which is in the world and does not fade out
淡入故事中的其他地方
Fade into some other place in the story
您基本上只是观看相同赛事的加速版本
You just basically watch a speed up version of the same events
这本身实际上是一项成熟的技术
Which which in itself is actually a full born technology that
你知道，我们必须设计、发明、原型
You know , we have to design , invent , prototype
人们必须这样做，这太疯狂了
People had to make this it's it's it's crazy
我我喜欢它
I i love it
别误会我的意思
Don't get me wrong
我喜欢它
I love it
但是是的
But yeah
你没有让自己变得容易
You did not make it easy for yourselves
是的
Yeah
不 。不，你知道我知道发生了什么事
No . don't , you know that i know what what's going on
但我们总是尽力让这变得更加
But we always though always try to make this the more
你知道，我们最后可以加入疯狂有趣的东西，对吧
You know , crazy fun stuff that we can in at the end , right
呃
Uh
是的
Yeah
然后，呃，就像人们之前提到过的那样
And then , uh , like people mentioned this before
就像这是一次疯狂的努力
Like it was a crazy more effort
事实上你有这个连续体实际上还在继续
And the fact that you have this continuit actually continue
这是你拥有的最昂贵的东西
It is the most expensive thing you have
所以当你用这种经典的电影语言
So when you in this classic cinematic language
你跳到特写
You jump to a close up
所以此时此刻，唯一的事情
So in this moment , the only thing
你必须为这个特写而感动和哭泣
You have to animate and cry about is this close up
而这个角色就在这里
And this one character right here
如果你有这样的没有完整
If you have like this no full
比如说广角镜头中的相机控制
Let's say like camera control in a wide shot as well
有时现在只有杰基
And sometimes right now it's only jackie
但我们也有类似的场景，你知道
But we have scenes with like , you know
免费四五个字符等等
Free four or five characters and so on
你需要管理这一切
And you need to manage all that
你不能只是想把某人从现场赶走
You cannot just like dispt someone from the scene
你知道，当玩家向左看时
You know , when the player is looking to the left
事实上我们和约翰尼一起做
Actually we do it with johnny
但假设他有一个特殊的地方纽约猫
But let's say he has like a special place new york cat
所以我们会看到，当你不再看约翰尼时，他总是消失
So we'll see that johnny always disappears when you stop looking at him
就像你转身一样
Like you turn around
你把他的枪转回来
You turn back his gun
但是为了，呃
But for , uh
我可以继续说一些离题的话，比如我们如何介绍
I could go on tangents about like how we introduce
就像乔纳斯一样，精疲力尽
And like sponning and spent out jonas
单独设计的自我，嗯
The separate design self , um
但还是喜欢制作
But still like making
你知道，当你想让npc出现在场景中时，要确保这种情况
You know , securing the situation that when you want npc in in the scene
他其实需要从夏天一路过来
He actually needs to come from summer all the way
坐下
Sit down
和你说话，搬进衣服上去
Talk with you , move into the clothes up
你知道，emt与脸有关
You know , emt with the face
然后站起来一路走到外面
And then get up and walk all the way out there
而你就让他消失了
And you just kind of disappear him
而且这个时候也不像切割啊,呃
And at this time it's also not like cutting , uh
npc和玩家之间来回
Between npc and player back and forth
因此，就像您只有有限数量的动画和信息可供出售一样
So at the same like you have just a limited amount of like animation and information to sell
如果你的镜头中有NPC
If you have npc that's in your shot
你知道，你不能只是坐着，一动不动
You cannot be just like sitting , you know , static
他有时需要移动，这样做
He needs to move sometimes do this
回去吧，你知道的
Go back like , you know
他做了一些东西
And he makes something
他基本上需要生活
He needs to live basically
不仅喜欢动画的连续性
And like also doing it not only like continuity of animation
但实时完成这一切也是一个问题
But also doing it all in a real time is an issue
因为话又说回来，当你想要场景时，例如
Because then again , when you want the scene , for example
我们演奏了分数现场
We played the score poscene
例如，你和杰基以及对饮料发表评论的女孩坐下来
And you sit down with jackie and the girl with the drinks comment , for example
或者稍后暴徒进来
Or later the goons come in
他们需要从像
And they need to go from like
从这个遥远的地方来到你身边
Come to you from this like distant part of location
你实际上可以在 lizzi 中看到远处的门
And you can actually see how the door far away in lizzi
但他们敞开心扉，一路走来
But they open , they walk all the way
但从我们的电影来看
But from our cinematic
假设过去需要完美的时机和节奏来实现这一切
Let's say perspective used to need the perfect timing and pacing for all of this
所以我们需要喜欢，你知道，适应它
So we need to like , you know , adjust for it
好的
Okay
因此，例如，他们需要大约三十五秒才能到达这里
So it will take them like thirty five seconds to get here , for example
当杰基喜欢的时候他们就会来
And they will come exactly when jackie is like
哦，现在他们打断了我等等
Oh , now they're interrupted me and so on
但你知道，你不只是按照镜头剪辑那样做
But you didn't just do it like , you know , along the camera edit
哦，他们在这里，这非常简单。所以是的
Oh they're here it's super simple . so yeah
像这样连续拍摄是一件很难做到的事情
This like this continuous camera shot is it was such a difficult thing to do
所以你有点抱歉
So you something i oh sorry
对不起
Sorry
哦不
Oh no
是的
Yeah
呃，继续
Uh , continue
呃，以公寓为例
Uh , here the apartment , for example
另一个案例
Another case
我不知道，呃，呃
I don't know , uh , uh
在这种情况下，哪些生命部件在正常情况下做出反应
Which life parts are replying in this case in norma
我认为你有一个很好的，呃
You have a good one , i think , uh
你也可以评论它
And you can comment on it as well
没关系
Never mind
所以英雄去公寓
So hero going to the apartment
你应该去保险箱
And you should go to the safe
呃，杰基所在的地方
Uh , place where jackie
所以当然那里有一个任务标记。杰基·兰斯在那里
So of course there's like a quest marker there . jackie lans there
去那里感觉有点明显
It feels kind of obvious to go there
但你也可以对 guana 发表评论
But you can comment on the guana as well
你可以去找你的无能者，呃
You can go to your inables , uh
床并从那里拿枪
The bed and take a gun from there
后面还有评论
And there's a comment back there
如果你这么做了又怎样
So what if you do it
就在杰基说另一句话的时候
Exactly when jackie is saying a different line
是否应该中断
Should it interrupt
你应该让他完成吗
Should you should he finished
但如果你说完然后你说的话听起来不像是一个正确的对话
But if you finishes and then you say it like it doesn't sound like a correct dialogue
所以也许中间应该有一条连接线之类的
So maybe there should be like a connection line in the middle and so on
但大多数人都看不到
But most of the pairs won't see it
因为他们只会做其他事情
Because they will just do something else
否则他们不会到达这个确切的位置
Or they will not hit this exact spot
当你击中它时
Where when you hit it
然后就像发生了不同的事情
Then like different things happen
从付款人的角度来看，这又是不可察觉的
And again it's imperceivable from the payer perspective
对于玩家来说应该永远都是这样完美、流畅、易懂的体验
For players should always be just like this perfect , fluent , understandable experience
是的
Yeah
哇
Wow
一
Um
是的
Yeah
我这这位老人最近特别重播
I this , this seniin particular replaying it recently
你知道，这让我震惊，因为它完成了我认为在电影中的事情
This struck me as , you know , accomplishing something that i think in cinema
您经常通过长镜头或不间断的单镜头来完成
You often accomplished with a long take or an unbroken single take
哪一个是紧张和悬念
Which is tension and suspense
而且，你知道，我想到了一部类似《人类之子》的电影
And , you know , i think about a movie like children of men
在那里你有这些非常长的不间断的长镜头
Where you have these really long unbroken long takes
它会让你体重增加
And it makes you weigh more
呃，担心角色
Uh , afraid for the characters
因为割伤或感觉不安全
Because there's no safety in cuts or feeling like
哦，也许编辑会以某种方式保存这些字符，比如，不
Oh , maybe somehow the edit will save these characters like , no
我们被困在这种纪录片风格中
We're locked in in this documentary style
而且，尤其是当抢劫案开始出现问题时
And , and especially when things start to go wrong here with the heist
事实上，我们已经建立了这种连续的
The fact that we've established this continuous
你无法逃脱这种长镜头风格
You can't escape it kind of long take style
我认为确实加剧了紧张气氛
I think really amps up the tension
一
Um
你也可能会谈论这个吗
And so did you might talk about that
你怎么样，如果你想过的话
How you , if you thought about
这是如何连续的第一人称视角，呃
How this continuous first person perspective , uh
你实际上也将它用于无法逃脱的电影技巧
You were using it actually also for the cinematic technique of no escape
你被锁在
You are locked in
这是实时的
This is real time
呃
Uh
你知道，在某种程度上
You know , in a way
这是你免费获得的东西
It's something you get for free
更重要的是你无法真正逃脱它
And even more you can't really escape it
因为一旦我们采用这个设计
Because once we go with this design
我们得到了一切酷炫的东西
We get everything that's like cool coming with it
所有这些，你知道，也有缺点，呃
And all that , you know , downsides , uh , as well
所以从某种意义上说它起作用了
So in some sense it worked
但例如，在其他方面
But for example , in others
事实上你只有副总裁是有问题的
The fact that you had just vp was problematic
因为也只是为了打断你的身体存在
Because also just to interrupt your body presence
看到一只手像这样移动
See a hand moving like along this
甚至更多。所以现在你会到达这里，还有一只手在你面前
and even more . so now you will get here there's also a hand in front of you
只是为了提醒您，您处于什么样的环境中
Just to remind you like what kind of context you are in
也在这里，例如
And also here , for example
当我们没有这只手的时候
When we didn't have this hand
感觉真的很奇怪。就像你只是太空中的这个浮点，没有参考
It felt really weird . like you were just this floating point in space without reference
坐下来感觉超级舒服
And sit felt like super off
你加上这手牌，突然间你就完全领先了
You add this hand and suddenly you're totally total leader
一
Um
例如，这个场景是关键情节点之一
And for example , this scene is one of the crucial plot points
就整个故事来说
Let's say in the whole story
所以我们觉得有必要
So it felt necessary for us
它至少需要是无钢的
It needs to be at least this steel free with like
你知道，你的焦点就在你面前
You know , your focus here in front of you
你需要感知它
You need to perceive it
我们不能给你自由
We cannot give you a freedom
例如旋转一百八十度
For example , rotating one hundred and eighty degrees
这太重要了
This is too important
就像从我们的角度来看
Like from our perspective
我们需要确保您看到它
We need to be sure that you see it
就像，呃，呃，同时感知到
And like , uh , uh , perceived at , at the same time
我们试着留下一点，嗯
We try to leave a little like , um
呃，玩家的互动性
Uh , interactivity for the players
例如，当你看这件夹克时
So when you look at the jacket , for example
我，呃
I , uh
你应该看看你
You should look at you for
呃，应该可以吗
Uh , should it work
也许现在还不是这个时刻
Maybe it's not this exact moment
因为我认为他在照顾明天
Because i think he was looking after tomorrow
哦这里，看，看，像你一样
Oh here , look , look , look as you
你看着他时会有这样的反应
It's such a reaction to you looking at him
但如果你不看着他，这一切就不会发生
But it wouldn't happen if you didn't look at him
嗯，我们在这里，呃，呃，也是takora的方式，呃
Um , here we , uh , uh , also the way that takora , uh
Takara takura 消失在画框后面
The takara takura disappears like behind the frame
然后突然出现在你面前
And then suddenly appears just in front of you
这是我们可以用这种有限的视角做的很酷的事情之一
It's one of the cool things we can do with like this limited perspective
呃，嗯，就像我们如何利用它一样
Uh , um , like how we can utilize that
你知道，创造，呃，创造戏剧
You know , to create , uh , to create drama
但现在回到我之前的想法
But now going back to my previous thought
所以有时候紧张是很酷的
So sometimes it's cool for tension
像你一样，你无法逃脱，你是
Like you , you cannot escape , you are
你知道，在这个地方。等等
You know , in this spot . and so on
但有时候，当你们的谈话时间较长时，例如
But sometimes when you have longer conversations that , for example
是更多的阐述而不是情感的沉重
Are a bit more exposition rather than emotion is heavy
这成为一个问题
It becomes a problem
因为内容越长，对玩家的吸引力就越低
Because the content , it can become less attractive for the player the longer it goes
因为你没有这么酷
Because you don't have all this cool
你知道，视觉效果来自不同的相机共享
You know , visuals coming from different camera shares
发送、编辑等
Send , edit , and so on
所以球员有时可以，你知道，那些在外的球员
So players sometimes can , you know , those away
然后我们需要
And then we need to
呃，比如让它更有吸引力
Uh , make it more attractive , for example
在动画层面上时刻保持内容一定程度的吸引力
On the level of animation to keep a certain level of attractivity of content at all times
所以如果场景很长并且很重要
So if there's a long scene and it's important
而你被锁在一个地方
And you are locked in one spot
我们需要投入更多资金，以其他方式使其更具吸引力
We need to invest more into making it attractive in some other way
也许有背景
Maybe with the background
也许随着灯光
Maybe with the lighting
也许有某种效果
Maybe with some kind of effex
可能是和角色的表演有关
Maybe with the character staging
时间越来越长，在一个地方持续的时间越来越长
And so long and the longer it goes in one spot
越长越需要开头也有这个场景
The longer the , the more you needed there's this scene at the beginning as well
嗯，在，呃，至少当你心情低落的时候是这样
Um , in the , uh , at least this when you're down at judbasement
并且在很长一段时间里
And for a really long time
你坐在这把椅子上
You are sitting in this chair
你可以看到伊芙琳的动作有多么像
And you can see how much like evelyn is moving
朱迪来回移动并再次回到你身边
Judy is moving back and forth and back to you again
因为如果他们只是在同一个地方
Because if they were just in the same spots
尽管这是一个有趣的序列
Even though it's an interesting sequence
它，它就变成了，实际上我们有这个
It , it just became , and actually we had this
变得有点乏味
It became a little bit tedious
例如，后来我们添加了伊芙琳
So for example , later we added eveline
拿起杯子并像与 deo 一样移动
Getting cup and moving like alongside deo
还因为框架比 更宽，呃
Also because the frame is wider than , uh
用一张相机拍摄就能看到什么
What you can see in like with one camera shot
所以你要么看到今天，要么看到伊芙琳
So you can either see today or evelyn
如果你非常关注朱迪
And if you pay a lot of attention to judy
我们需要提醒您现场的证据
We needed to remind you that evidence in scene as well
于是她起身
So she got up
来回走在你面前
Walked in front of you back and forth
因为她不耐烦所以有动力
And it's motivated because she's impatient
她想要效果或者什么
She wants effects or , or something
但是，嗯
But , um
但是是的
But yeah
我不知道它要去哪里
I don't know where it's going
但是，呃，这个想法
But , uh , the thought
但是，呃，还是，嗯
But , uh , still , um
保留内容的要点
The point of keeping the content
对于 fbp 设计来说，始终具有吸引力确实至关重要
Attractive at all times was really crucial for this fbp design
因为我们失去了一些东西
Because we lose something
所以我们需要想办法弥补
So we need to somehow make up for it
所以我们通常可以使用的最大工具当然是交互性和反应性，对吧
So of course to biggest tools that we can use normally are interactivity and reactivity , right
因此，交互性是指你实际上可以做一些对世界有益的事情
So interactivity is when you actually can do something that is towards the world
反应性是你需要相反的方式
And reactivity is you need the other way around
所以言语会对你所做的一切做出反应
So words react to you doing whatever
这实际上是一个有趣的例子
This is actually an interesting example
因为理论上
Because in theory
这是一个非常被动的场景吧
This is a very passive scene , right
你基本上已经脚踏实地了
You are basically grounded in the situation
也许因为你正站在这个非常
Maybe because you are standing in this very
呃
Uh
精致，呃，有的地方，有的地方，呃
Delicate , uh , spots to be , to be in , uh
不过，如果你观察玩家对这个场景的反应，就会发现，速度很快
Still , if you watch how players react to this scene , it's it's , it's fast
他们认为，你知道
They think that , you know
他们深吸一口气
They take a deep breath
当 takaoa 真正接近时
When takaoa is actually close
离玻璃非常非常近
Very , very close to the , to the glass
他们实际上对这些聋人做出反应
They actually react to , to , to , to these deaf
我认为是，呃
I i think it's , uh
我想当它起作用时
I think when it works
效果真的非常好
It works really , really well
呃
Uh
这是我想触摸他们的东西
And this is something i wanted to touch them
因为我们，我们发现，我猜，呃
Because we , we discovered , i guess , uh
这种沉浸感使一切倍增
That immersion multiplies everything
因此，如果您有精彩的内容呈现在玩家面前
So if you have a great content in front of the player
然后他们实际上非常投入
Then they actually are extremely engaged
如果你真的给他们一些东西去做一些非常有趣、有吸引力、有趣的事情
If you actually give them something to do something very fun , engaging , interesting
他们继续参与游戏
They stay engaged with the game
他们非常融入体验之中
And they are very much inside the inside the experience
另一方面，当你不再拥有那样的东西时
On the other hand , when you don't have that again
沉浸让一切倍增
Immersion multiplies everything
所以你可能会遇到很大的问题
So you can have very big problems
如果有什么事，你知道
If something just , you know
玩得不好
Does does not play well
正确的
Right
因为归根结底，这只是一场游戏
Because at the end of the day , it's a game
我们需要能够玩这个游戏
We need to be able to play this game
甚至在这个特别的时刻
And even this in this specifically a moment
这种互动量
This amount of interactivity
所以玩家实际上可以移动相机
So player actually you can move the camera
并且，你知道，制定行动
And , you know , frame the action
他们想要如何构建它很重要
How they want to frame it is important
它实际上运作得足够好
It actually works well enough
所以玩家仍然在这个游戏中
So the player is still inside this game
他们相信正在发生的事情
They believe in what's happening
他们，他们感觉是对的
They , they feel it right
他们实际上是这整个经历中的演员
They actually are actor inside this , this whole experience
不仅是从这里出发的观察者能够看到
Not only an observer that goes from this got eyes view
你知道，看着蚂蚁光滑地走
You know , watching as the ants smooth
不，他们实际上正处于其中
No , they actually are in the middle of it
他们
They
好吧，他们充当玩家
Well , they act as the player
作为玩家颜色角色
As the player color character
不是相反
Not the other way around
一、和、一
Um , and , um
一
Um
对于，呃，对于，例如
For , uh , for , for example
，这个就像这样工作
The , the this like for this to work
你需要资金才能让玩家站在学校的角度
You need dough to put the player in the school perspective
哪个有吸引力
Which is attractive for
例如
So for example
我记得场景的第一次迭代
I remember that the first iterations of the scene
我们看着整个事件，就像从一本杂志上想象谋杀案一样
We were watching the whole like think of the murder from like a magazine
这就是我们这样称呼它的，你知道，半地板
This how we call it like this , you know , semi floor
让我们说通过一些，嗯，通过一些东西
Let's say through some like , um , like through something
而且他们真的很远
And they were really far away
而且场景没有发挥作用
And the scene didn't work
因为真的很长
Because it's really long
我想大概持续了四分钟
Like it goes for like four minutes , i think
当角色很小的时候，呃
And when the characters are small , uh
就在那里，你就在那里，呃
And out there and you are , uh
你知道，就像被迫一样，观看它
You know , like forced to , to watch it
它突然变成了一种非常沉闷的经历
It suddenly became a really dull experience
所以我们需要，我们需要发明一些东西来让你尽可能接近动作
So we need , we needed to invent something to bring you as close to the action as possible
还有那面威尼斯镜子，呃，呃，呃，主意
And hands that venetian mirror , uh , uh , uh , idea
以及它的案例
And the case by it
正是这样的情况，就像这里面的一些人所做的那样
It was exactly cases like those were like some people in this to do it
就像 fpp 无法工作一样
Like no way fpp can work
因为就像你怎样才能做到
Because like how can you do it
但事实证明，你可以通过对不同事物的相似观点获得真正的创造力，嗯
But then it turns out you can get really creative with like points of view on different things , um
而且只要内容和故事实际上是有创意的
And also as long as actually the content and stories is creative
也喜欢玩家可以，嗯，嗯
Also like players can , um , um
呃呃呃比赛ch呃
Uh , uh , uh , the match ch , uh
你可以像很多人一样原谅你，呃
You can forgive you like a lot of , uh
很多事情有时甚至可能不是你实际上会做的最合乎逻辑的事情
A lot of things sometimes even it's not maybe the most logical thing that you would actually do
从外面观看这一切
And watching this in from outside
但如果它对我有吸引力呢
But what if it's attractive for me
喜欢它的作品。人们并没有真正考虑过它
Like it works . people don't really think about it
我觉得这很酷
And i think it's cool
是的
Yeah
我是说，我，我记得这个场景就像
I mean , i , i remember this scene being like a
就像我脑子里有一件大事
Like a big deal in my brain
我第一次玩的时候，就像我一样
The first time i was playing it , like i
我真的很喜欢它
I was really into it
我真的很享受
I was really enjoying it
但当那一幕发生时
But when that scene happened
我想那是我开始喜欢充分欣赏的时候，呃
I think that's when i started to like fully appreciate , uh
所有这些事情如何结合在一起创造了这种被困的体验
How all these things were coming together to create this experience of feeling trapped
感觉就像我不能你知道，我无法移动
Feeling like i can't you know , i can't move
我发不出声音
I can't make a sound
我和杰基在这里
I'm in here with jackie
就像我非常感受到那种存在
Like i very much feel that presence
然后也像你说的那样欣赏
And then also appreciating like you were saying
亚历克斯是那种擅长长镜头的人
Alex is the kind of long take kness of this
这么长的时间里发生了很多事情
It is this long seeing where a lot happens
人们进进出出
People come in and out
这是一个感人至深的呻吟场景
It's a moan emotional scene
有人死了，就像所有这一切都以不间断的方式发生一样
somebody dies like all of that happening in an unbroken way
表演必须喜欢流动
Where the performances have to like flow
总的来说，没有删减，没有作弊
Altogether there's no cuts there's no cheating
一
Um
是的
Yeah
我就是这么感觉
I just feel like that
这对我来说是第一个华丽的时刻
That was the first like flashy moment for me
我就像，哦哇
I'm like , oh wow
如果你继续玩这个游戏，这就像你所期待的那样
This is like what you are in store for if you keep playing this game
我真的真的很感激
And i just really , really appreciate it
明确涉及此的所有工作
All the work clearly that went into this
是的
Yeah
正确的
Right
就像我一样，我作为一名球员突然意识到了
Like i , i as a player suddenly became conscious of like
哦我，我开始明白这里发生了什么
Oh i , i'm starting to see what's happening here
这就像我以前从未经历过的真正的第一人称体验
This is like a true first person experience in a way that i don't think i've had before
并且，并且看到了。是的
And , and that seen . yeah
这就像一个结晶时刻，这就是可能的
It was like a crystallization moment of this is what's possible
当你致力于这种不间断的体验时
When you commit to this unbroken experience
嗯，不过很酷，呃，我认为这对每个人来说都不是非常直观
Um , cool though , uh , i think it wasn't super intuitive for everyone
例如，很有趣
For example , was interesting
我喜欢看很多信任游戏
I like i watched a ton of played trust
就像我喜欢看人们如何玩游戏一样
Like i love to watch how people play the game
我也从中学到了
And also i learned from it like
我们可以改进什么，呃，下次更好
What could we improve , uh , better next time
比如说，在《甜蜜的索拉》中
And for example , in the sweet sora
我看到很多人们喜欢的地方
I saw plenty of play rose where people like
它们挤在相机内部就像居中关闭一样
They squeeze inside the camera is like centered shut
他们在整个场景中都保持这样的状态
And they leave it like this throughout rest of the scene
他们不喜欢碰这样的东西
They don't like touch them such thing
有时他们可能喜欢触摸，你知道，那根小鸟的棍子
Sometimes they like maybe touch the , you know , the stick a little bird
就像刷新一样
So like it's refresh
但他们却真的跟着行动。等等
But they really follow the action . and so on
所以我觉得，嗯
So i feel that , um
其实我不知道我对此有何感受
Actually i don't know how i feel about it
只是我从一开始就对每个人来说并不是超级直观
It's just that this i wasn't super intuitive for everyone from the start
这就像进入内部，呃，就像进入身体内部一样
And this like going inside it was , uh , like inside the body
就像，你知道，真正关注事物
And like , you know , really paying attention to things
我认为人们仍然习惯于，你知道，一旦像某些东西触发一样
I think people are still used that , you know , once like something triggers
通常你把垫子收起来
Usually you put the pad away
就像，你知道，游戏发生了
And just like , you know , the game happens
白色上的一些东西
Whiting some things on p
我们上演了他们
We staged them
所以你必须移动相机
So you had to move the camera
因为我们想吸引你
Because we wanted to engage you
但后来我看到角色的电镀者刚刚走出画面
But then i watch the platers for characters just walk out of frame
是的 。就这样，然后他们就开始说话了，你知道，就像在银幕外一样
Yeah . that's it then they talk , you know , from like offscreen
我就像旋转相机
And i'm like rotate the camera
请喜欢这显然只是为了 st
Please like it's obvious just for the st
但现在就这样结束了
But now it just finishes like this
好吧
And well
该，该，该，该
The , the , the , the
这个设计的那些元素
The , the those elements of this design
我，我，我真的，我真的很喜欢我们所做的事情
Which i , i , i really , i really like what we've done
呃，乍一看并不明显，对吧
Uh , that are not obvious at the first glance , right
例如
For example
事实上，你实际上可以像以前一样在时间选择期间保持安静
The fact that you can actually stay quiet during time choices like did
你知道吗
Did you know about that
我的意思是，这实际上是我们支持moi的一个选择
I mean , it's an actually an option that we support moi
每时每刻都在思考，对吗？
Think all all the time , like every time , right
呃
Uh
所以，但是人们，人们是，是
So , but but people , people are , are
你知道，是由这样的想法触发的，嘿
You know , are are triggered by the idea that , hey
我有时间真正下来
I have time actually going down
所以我必须选择一些东西，对吧
So i have to pick something , right
不，你是，你是演员
No , you are , you are the actor
如果你不想说什么
If you don't want to say anything
出色地
Well
什么也别说。或者就像自我说的
Don't say anything . or like ego said
如果你有这个，这个视图
If you have this , this view
其实你可以四处看看，呃
You can actually well look around , uh
就像莉兹凉亭里的自我一样
And like ego set in the lizz bower
当你遇见朱迪，你就遇见了，呃，伊芙琳
When you meet judy and you meet , you meet , uh , evelyn
这是被设计成这样工作的东西
This is something that is designed to , to work like that
所以你实际上可以看看，看看之前的每件事
So you can actually look at , look at every everything before
而且，你知道，也许他们会做出反应
And , you know , maybe they will react
也许不是
Maybe not
但这实际上是我们有意识的设计和决定，为玩家提供这种
But it's actually conscious design and decision on our part to give the player this kind of
出色地
Well
他们拥有的自由和他们必须做的自由
Freedom that they have that they have to
或者至少不能以某种创造性的方式来增强玩游戏的整体体验
Or cannot at least use in some creative way to enhance the whole experience of playing the game
因为到了游戏的最后，这就是游戏
Because at the very end of the game , this is a game
所以没有过场动画
So there are no cutscenes
有场景。场景是为了播放而制作的，嗯
There are scenes . and scenes are made to be played , um
我想我们还是这样，呃
I think it's something we're still like , uh
以某种方式学习
Learning in a way
是你，抱歉，回到开头，就像，呃
It's the u , sorry , going back to the beginning of the start , like , uh
我们在这场比赛中的所有比赛方式是，嗯
The way we approached through all playing in this game was , um
也不仅仅是站在像，嗯
Was also not only on the side of like , um
做出影响世界的重大选择
Making the big choices that affect the world
就像，你知道的，把任务分成前面的过去等等
And like , you know , split the quest into the front past and so on
但也有很多喜欢那些小的个人选择
But also plenty of like those small personal choices
当你喜欢角色扮演角色时，它真的就像超级关键
When you like role playing the character without it's really being like super crucial
就像你想如何表达自己一样
It's just like how you want to express yourself
举例来说，所有那些你可以保持沉默的时间选择
So for example , all those time choices when you can stay silent
你可以保持沉默。角色会对它做出反应，就像
You can stay silent . and characters will react to it like
哦，例如，你不太爱说话
Oh you're not much of a talker , for example
并且不需要分割任务
And it doesn't necessary split the quest
但它让你对自己在这个世界上的身份有一点点不同的认识
But it gives you like a little bit of different flink of who you are in this world
以及总是放弃游戏
As well as like always drop the game
例如，您可以拒绝饮酒
You can refuse drinking , for example
我认为是由其中一位qs提出的
something i think was proposed by one of the qs
谁像直尺那样哈哈哈哈哈哈
Who's like a straight edge that ha ha ha ha ha ha
其实喜欢有机会
Actually love to have a portunity
是的
Yeah
喜欢随时拒绝喝酒
To like to decline drinks at all times
我们在整场比赛中都坚持这样做
And we went with it throughout the whole game
你可以拒绝每次喝酒
You can decline drink every single time
只是为了能够喜欢用这种，呃，用这种方式表达自己
Just to be able to like express yourself in this , uh , in this way
所以不幸的是有很多非常小的选择
So there's a lot of really tiny choices that unfortunately
我觉得他们并没有真正被视为选择
I feel they weren't really perceived as choices
因为通常球员都会期望不同的工作人员会产生很多后果
Because usually players exuh expect a lot of consequences to different staff
为什么我们创建这一层
Why we created this layer
也就像，我知道喝醉了哈哈，就是这样，你是一个喝酒的角色
Also of just like , i know taking a rk ha ha that's it you're a drinking character
是的
Yeah
或者你可以真正专注于，你知道的，npc，嗯
Or you can just can be really focused on , you know , npc , um
我认为我们仍在学习如何做得更好
And i think it's something we're still learning how to do it better
呃
Uh
比如说个人角色扮演层
How to like make this let's say personal role playing layer
甚至对于玩家来说更酷
Even like cooler for the , for the player
呃，为了让玩家能够享受到更多的乐趣
Uh , for the players to enjoy more
一
Um
但这是我们采用这种设计的第一款游戏
But it was our first game in this design
所以我觉得一些错误肯定会发生
So like i feel some mistakes were bounds to happen
或者就像上课一样
Or just like lessons
我觉得这也许很有趣
I think it's interesting maybe
呃，想想我们的例子
Uh , to think that in our case
甚至诸如玩家的视线或玩家站立的位置之类的事情
Even things like where the player looks or where the player stands
或者怎么样，多远还是多远
Or how , how far or how far
他们与npc的接近程度也可以作为一个表达载体吧
How close they are to npc can also be used as an expression vectors , right
作为可以定义他们关系的东西
As something that can define their relationship
或者至少他们想如何接近这个人
Or at least how they want to approach this person
所以当我们，你知道，设计整个系统时
So when we were , you know , designing the whole system
那么几年前
So years ago
我一直牢记着这样一个想法：你应该遇到一个实际上非常重要的人
I always had in mind this idea that you are supposed to meet someone that's actually very important
我们被告知
And we are being told
不要看着他们的眼睛
Do not look them in the eye
当然，你知道，你，你可以做到这一点
And of course , you know , you , you can do that
事实上，你可以通过观察他们的另一只脚来环顾四周
You can actually look at their other feet to look look around them
但我们实际上可以对玩家做出反应
But we can actually react to player
直视他们的眼睛
looking straight in their eye
并且实际上以支持该播放器的方式分支内容
And actually branch the content in a way that supports this player
那其实是不想听游戏
That actually does not want to listen to the game
即使不是，你知道，这不是选择集上的选择对了一半
Even though it's not , you know , it's not choice on that choice set choice half right
这实际上不是你从列表中选择的东西
it's not something that you pick from a list is actually
你在场景中的行为决定了世界对你的反应
How you behave inside the scene that defines the reactivity of the world towards you
实际上再次让你融入游戏
And actually again grounds you in the game
并让你再次成为
And allows you to be again
场景内的演员
An actor inside the scene
而且不仅仅是一个从中挑选的观察者，你知道
And not only an observer that picks from , you know
绿色、红色、蓝色选择
Green , red , blue choices
因为我们是，所以我们知道如何做到这一点
Because we are , we understand how to make this
这是新的部分，实际上非常困难
This is the new part that actually extremely difficult
但好吧
But well
好玩吧
Fun , right
凉爽的
Cool
呃
Uh
这正是我们在其他场合所看到的
This is exactly what we mon for other occasions
就像餐厅旁边的这个jackie之类的
It's like this jackie by the restaurant and so on
就像是你通过等待一段时间或朝某个特定方向看而做出的选择
Like it's the choices you make just by like waiting a little bit longer or looking in a particular direction
或者进入某个特定的空间
Or entering a particular space
这不是列出的选择之一
It's not one of those like listed choices
人通常都是坚持不懈的
People usually persive
哦，这个游戏没有选择
Oh , there are no choices in this game
因为游戏就像往常一样会尽力做到这一点
because the game like usually it would try to make it
所以它会以一种你看不到的方式调整你的行为
So it adjust to your behavior in a way that's certainly invisible for you
也为了你
And for you
就像是线性的
It's like it's linear
就像，你知道，现在有一个问题
Like , you know , there are a tosis now
其实如果你愿意的话，如果你和他一起去的话
Actually if you like , if you went with him
你会有一个不同的分支
You would have a different branch
你只是不太喜欢
You just didn't really like
难道你不认为这是一个选择吗
Didn't you perceive it as a choice
你只是以某种方式做到了
You just did it in a way
正确的
Right
是的
Yeah
我认为这就是我真正欣赏的事情
And i think that's like the thing that i really appreciate about
对这个游戏很欣赏，也很欣赏
Appreciate about this game and appreciated it
最喜欢玩的时间越长的就是像所有这些，所有这些你的样子
The most like the longer played is like all these , all these ways that you are
呃，影响v的体验
Uh , affecting the experience of v
以及你的塑造方式
And how you're shaping
你知道，这个故事以这些微妙的方式
You know , the story in these subtle ways
就像你说的喝酒的事
The drinking thing like you mentioned
我我喜欢那一刻
I , i like that moment
我总是像
I always am like
我想喝吗
Do i want to drink
就像，就像提出这个选项让我进行自我反思
Like , like presenting that option makes me kind of self reflect
所以这就像一种吸引玩家的方式
So it's like a way of almost like drawing the player in
让他们思考正在发生的事情
And making them think about what's going on
一
Um
所以我们对着直边大喊
So we shout out to the straight edge
一
Um
但是是的
But yeah
所以，当我们结束时
So , so as we're wrapping up
我，你知道，我，我真的很喜欢看为什么要玩这个
And i , you know , i , i really love watching why play through this
而且我确信玩游戏比呃，过场动画更有压力，嗯
And i'm sure it's more stressful to play through gameplay than uh , the cinematics , um
但是，像这样结束
But to , to kind of wrap up like what
对你们来说最大的收获是什么
What for you guys is like the biggest takeaway
或者最大的收获之一
or one of the biggest takeaways
你已经从这次经历中吸取了教训
You've had as far as like learning from this experience
在未来的项目中你会随身携带的东西
Something that you're gonna take with you in future projects
也许你，你不知道要进入这个
That maybe you , you didn't know going into this
显然，小伙子们学到了很多东西
Clearly there's guys learned a lot
听起来好像发现了很多东西
It sounds like and discovered a lot of things
但有一件事是什么呢
But what's one thing
也许你会从中带走
Maybe that that you're gonna take away from this
你有我有的东西
You have i have like semme something
所以我，好吧
So i , okay
所以，但你继续思考
So , but you keep thinking
嗯，好吧
Um , all right
所以，嗯
So , um
好的
Okay
它
It
但这在某种程度上听起来可能很平庸，或者是非常明显的事情
But it , it may sound banal in a way or something that's like super obvious
你知道，事后看来等等
You know , in hindsight and so on
但是呃，所有场景的最佳效果是那些你喜欢投入情感的场景
But uh , the best effects for all the scenes are the ones you are like emotionally engaged in
我知道这是一些超级
And i know it's some superva
但是一旦你和npc建立了关系
But once you create the relationship with the npc
而这个npc给人的感觉就是，呃，啊，人类
And this npc feels like , uh , ah human
这些就像游戏中所有最强大的时刻都像在那些个人路线上
These are like all the strongest moments in the game are like on those personal lines
就像从我的角度来看，就像我有点喜欢这个情节一样
Like from my perspective , like i kind of like the plot
超级复杂
It's super complicated
呃
Uh
我认为并且喜欢这很酷
I think and like it's cool
你知道这是赛博朋克情节
You know it's the cyber punk plot
还有那些最高的网络任务，一些东西
And those highest missions cyber something , something
但所有最感动的时刻
But all the most touching moments
我个人最喜欢这个游戏的所有东西都是个人的东西
And all the things i personally like most about this game is all the personal stuff
就像巴拿马和咖喱一样
Like with with panam and curry
所有与故事脱节的时刻等等
All the moments that are like mostly disconnected from the story and so on
这是像你这样的人，不会碰你或喜欢你，呃
It's someone like you , no touching you or like , uh
接吻或只是坐在一起
Kissing or just like sitting next to each other
壁炉旁边。等等
Next to the fireplace . and so on
一切，一切都一样，嗯，随着这个身体的存在
All , all the like , um , with this body presence
想想所有这些，比如与其他角色的接触和联系
Think all that like the touches and connection with other character
当你把它放在画布上时
And also when you put it on the canvas
有些人不喜欢赛博朋克，因为每个人都像，你知道的，在某种程度上孤独
Some dislike cyber punk quirt where everyone are like , you know , alone in a way
和其他一切一样，距离遥远、风雨无阻
And like every other super distant and suding
当一个喜欢的人真正关注你时
When someone like really pays attention to you
就像你在他们眼中看到的那样
And like you see it in their eyes
他们触碰你之类的东西
And they touch you and something
它变得如此、如此神奇
It becomes something so , so magical
所以对我来说
So for me
我认为最大的收获就是永远不要
I think the biggest takeaway is to never
曾经忘记过NPC和玩家之间的那些私人联系的时刻吗
Ever forget about those moments of personal connection between npc and player
并不是像我和某人一起做很酷的事情
Not that just like i do cool stuff with someone
有这样的阴谋，我们打倒这个组织
And there's this plot and we take down this organization is
为什么对我来说有意义
Why is it meaningful for me
为什么对npc有意义
Why is it meaningful to npc
NPC，相信我
The npc , trust me
我不能让他失望。等等
I cannot let him down . and so on
这是我要说的第一件事吗？
And is this first one thing i would say that would be my eoy
我知道这可能是非常明显的
I know it's like maybe it's super obvious
就像，嗯，事后看来
Like , um , in hindsight
但这是，是的
But this is , yeah
有时，最简单的回顾显而易见的事情是最重要的教训，很容易被忽视
Sometimes the simplest retrospect obvious things are the most important lessons that are easy to lose sight of
所以我想，是的，这是一个很好的教训
So i think , yeah , that's a great lesson
一
Um
我认为之后
I think that after
你知道，在开发这个游戏这么多年之后
You know , after working on this game for so many years
事实上在发布之后
And actually after releasing it
有了这个之后，这次要真正反思一下了
And after having this , this time to actually reflect on it
一
Um
我明白这就是什么时候、什么时候
I understand that this is when , when
当你真正从这个角度去制作游戏时
When you actually make a game from this perspective
这与其他游戏并不是同一场比赛
It's not really the same race as , as do other games
如果你明白我的意思的话，就像你一样，汽车和火车是不同的
If you know what i mean , like you like a car is a different than the train
还有，还有，还有，你知道，还有
And , and , and , and you know , and
还有、还有侧边自行车就在那里
And , and and side bicycle right there
您可以在其中讲述精彩的故事
There are stories that you can tell great in the
使用正常的古典叙事方式
Using the normal classical way of narration
我认为有很多
And i think there are very
非常有趣的故事，你只能使用第一人称或最好的故事
Very fun stories that you can only or best tale using this first person
呃，叙述类型
Uh , type of narration
我觉得你真的可以为两者制作同样的游戏
And i feel that you can really make the same game for , for both
你知道，在这两种情况下事情的运作方式并不相同，呃
You know , like things don't work the same way in both cases , uh
我们正在学习反方法来处理这种类型
And we are learning counter to approach this this type
这很令人兴奋，因为这对我们来说是全新的领域
And it's exciting because it's completely new territory for us
我也这么认为
It's something that i think that , well
我们以前绝对不会这么做，这是肯定的，呃
We would never did before that's for sure , uh
但我觉得里面的深度实在是太疯狂了
But i feel that there's just crazy amount of depth
桌子上还剩下
Still left on the table
以及我们可以接近的事情
And things that we can approach
现在我们明白了，我们拥有所有的工具，对吗？
And we understand now that we , we have all the tools , right
因为我们创造了设计
Because we created designs
我们创造了工具
We created tools
我们创造了处理事物的方法
We created approaches to things
我们创建了整个疯狂的经验团队，他们是他们所做的事情中最好的，对吗？
We created whole insane experience team that is the best of what at what they do , right
现在我觉得我们正处于做事的边缘
And right now i feel that we are at this very edge of doing
你知道，这样做甚至可以做得更好
You know , doing even that doing stuff even better
实际上，直接为这种特定类型的体验创建游戏
And actually creating a game straight up for , for this specific type of experience
你知道，就像讲述一个只能以这种特定方式讲述的故事一样
You know , like for telling a story that can only be told in this specific way
我认为这个独一无二
I think this unique
我认为这对我作为一名设计师和创作者来说非常令人兴奋
I think this is very exciting for me as a designer , as a creator
作为一个失去精彩内容的人
As a , as a person that los amazing content
呃
Uh
我想这就是我的收获
So that's that's my take take away , i guess
是的
Yeah
太棒了
That's awesome
我真的很兴奋
I'm really excited
呃，是的
Uh , yeah
是的
Yeah
我再次听到这一切
Just hearing all that i again
这是一个非常独特的
It was a really like unique
玩这个的体验很棒
Awesome experience playing through this
我对接下来的事情感到兴奋
I'm excited for what's next
很明显这是，呃
And it's very clear that this is , uh
当你做得好的时候，你所做的事情是完全看不见的
What you guys do when you do it well is completely invisible
所以我很高兴你们能够分享所有这些技术
So i'm so glad that you guys got to share all of these techniques
如果我们能够窥探这一切的幕后真相
And if we got to peek behind the curtain of everything that goes into to all of this
一
Um
所以是的
So yeah
保罗的自我
Paul ego
非常感谢你们加入我们
Thank you guys so much for joining us
有你真是太好了
It's been really great to have you
嗯，超级酷
Um , super cool
感谢大家的支持，团结起来才能谈论这个
Thanks for the support unity to be able to talk about this
因为这对我们来说也是第一次
Because it's also first time for us
所以我们对能够做到这一点感到非常兴奋
So we are super stoked to be able to do it
而且，呃，用印度语，呃，向我们所有的团队大声喊叫
And , uh , in indian , uh , huge shout out to all of our team
因为他们从来没有发生过任何思考游戏
Because nothing thinking game they've ever happens
喜欢单独或由一个人
Like by itself or by one person
唯一的集体努力
The sole collective effort
所以无论是电影伊拉克还是整个def团队
So both to cinematic iraq and the whole def team
老实说，实际上是世界上最有才华的人
Actually the most talented people in the world , honestly
所以谢谢，呃，也谢谢你的播客
So thanks , uh , and thank you for the podcast as well
惊人的
Awesome
是的
Yeah
我们的荣幸
Our pleasure
凉爽的
Cool
呃，嗯，是的
Uh , well , yeah
谢谢大家的观看
Thank you everybody for watching
这是我们关于赛博朋克二十七十七的对话
This has been our conversation on cyber punk twenty seventy seven
我们将在下一个视频中见到您
And we will see you in the next video
再见，伙计们
Bye guys